That is wrong.
The rhythm, yeah, yeah, yeah, whoa
Hearts in the balance, every card an open door
Feel the romance in every arcane world
One second
Out here in the wild wild streams
Where the trolls lurk deep and the chats still be
I'll survive so true, that's all because of every single one of you.
Vita, my sweetheart, Persian Queen Delight.
With your laugh so loud, you light up the night.
Page with the heart and the jokes that land.
Blonde bombshell with a beer in hand.
flop now we
you turn up
Okay, sorry, my phone all of a sudden
Masking tape or something that's bad. Well, what am I gonna do here?
Well, that's not very good though. Hold on. I just got another thing about this thing
But it's like I bought it. It was like pretty cool, but on Amazon, but it's like it doesn't fit the tablet
And that's the only that's the tickets to get there shit. Hey, can I do this?
Fuck well, what do I need to do?
Hi guys
Hi, sorry, do you hear me? How's your day?
Okay. Hi everybody. He's you gay. Yeah
Tell me tell me something. I don't know
Just kidding. I don't know if he is
Guys look my apartment's a clean. It's like not like perfect, but I mean there's stuff on the table, of course
I like it's like pretty clean though
Look good hi
Okay, why are you trying to fix this thing? Okay, it's like it doesn't it's not staying in this little tripod thing
I have because it's like the screw and it's worn off and so it's not fucking really not saying anymore
But it used to be able to oh, hold on. You got it my ball. Okay. There we go. Thank you. I try
Okay guys
Yeah, very sensitive, okay, but my fall, but we'll see
Okay, so
How are you guys doing? Oh welcome. It's gonna be Friday night. It was we got freaky Friday
I have the banner freaky Friday. You have a banner
Yeah
Okay, so freaky Friday. I don't know and I like the blue and the red because somehow
Similar to like some others. Okay, so hold on. So let's go. Yeah, let's go. Okay. Let's see
Keep a blinker
It's just my I have this alien my little alien friend
I need to friend
Absolutely love
Like that. Hey, what's up guys?
Yeah, so I spent a little time cleaning and take a little nappy
I'm about to grab a beer or Bruce key. I can get this and abuse just so perfect. Okay, please come on. Stay please
Maybe if I go like this one. Oh
I'm brilliant. I'm brilliant guys. I think I actually might be smart. I figured out. I figured it out. Now. It's like perfect
Yeah
And at the other way, okay
There's Lola shit, okay, sorry guys. Oh
Oh, oh shit. It's pulled out of the wall. Oh shit. I pulled up the thing guys. I'm a disaster right now
Just to do this bear with me one second. There we go
You know lights are cool. Yes, it's funky got this for me
So awesome. Thank you intracable. We fixed my
Flag and then it was all good guys almost there. Sorry. I just thought a little bit little bit frenzy, but
Whoo, yeah, I'm having a good good, uh, I
Want to put I want to have eventually have the alien behind me like I want to be like I don't know
I'll sit like over against here. Maybe I have the alien. Yeah
Everybody, okay, so here's what I need to do. I need to change the camera around
Oh
I'm here. I'm here. I think that's okay. There we go. Oh
How are we doing guys? Okay, so
You think so we're gonna do
Cards again, I just arranged like so many decks of cards. I said they're all organized. It's really cool
The whole table is I think I'm a kitchen. It's like it's not having this clean in like a long time
Am I looking okay?
Like I kind of got told by somebody
that I'm looking a little bit like bad.
Am I looking bad?
I don't know.
Maybe I do go a little bit hard on YouTube
and sometimes I do not like, you know,
my hair's a little messy, I'm not allowed to shave it
but am I that bad?
I don't know.
So we were reading about Leo yesterday.
I just want to finish this up with Leo.
Is anybody a Leo in the room?
There's any Leo. Oh, thank you Ingle. No, we're doing Fergo. We're doing Fergo. Any Fergo's in the room. Thank you. I'm trackable
Or if you want to sit someone shout out your sign and I can read a little bit about your sign
This is the dark side of the sign. This is called the
Dark side of strategy. It's called born on a rotten day, but it's not no day is really rotten, but
This is the kind of good because enough kind of humorous way though. Yeah
The dark side of the zodiac sign, but I can read that for you guys. I can do some of the card readings
If you would like a card reading tonight
Longer than just a free one you'd like to come on the panel. You can have longer on the panel. Okay, I can put some cash
up for that also I
Will open the panel
For a $10 sponsorship from me any one person I will open it for
for two hours. Okay? Okay, hold on one second.
Okay, there you go. Thank you. Thank you so much. I look good. Okay. Thank you. If someone threw out their sign,
I'm gonna read about your sign.
Yeah, and you know, I just have to like the panels have just been a little bit too much for me lately. They've just been a little bit.
That's kind of a little bit.
of an uncomfortable vibe.
And so I'm just, I think I'll have me
to be a little bit encouraged,
encouraged to start opening the panel up
because I'm happy just to come sharing
like the books and stuff.
Hey, baby.
But whatever you guys want to do,
I'm down.
Okay, so we're going to shout out.
Shout out your style.
Oh, where's my glasses?
I need my glasses.
it wipes with that. Yeah, so I'm gonna get, oops, I'm getting another pair of these glasses.
I mean, it's called like the Jeffrey, the Jeffrey Dahmer style. I'm getting like that. I think the
aviators have some reading glasses. I think they're about 20 bucks. I need another pair, plus
I think that will, this will look pretty funny on me. What do you think?
I did find a good pair. So here we go. There.
Okay, okay
I think the lights a little bit off and I look a little bit weird do I hold on from this light up
Okay, okay you guys
So there's so much died out yours a sign even if it's not just I thought I signed you one in here
Maybe it's your spouses or something like that. You know, I could tell you
the dark side of the gender of that sign.
And so you can hear if it kind of matches up,
if you're married to one, it will say,
if you're in love with one, and we'll talk about it.
So I'm kind of, you know, in their astrology,
so very generally, it might resonate, it might not.
But I think it was fun doing it.
It was a good book.
I need to get another one of these dark-sized astrology.
Let me see, I have any.
Like he after dark. Yeah, tonight's gonna be the freaky. We're gonna have a little bit. I don't know if I have a freak out
But it was you know, I think that's a little bit maybe much for the show, but
You know
We'll see. Hey, let's see. I'm looking for a vacuum. So I need maybe a new vacuum cleaner. How much does this one cost?
Thirty dollars featherweight
the witching hour approaches, who, I don't know,
I really got afraid of witches, I've actually,
known a few, yeah, let's see,
I'm looking for a vacuum case, what was I saying,
I'm gonna get something else, I'll get the glasses.
There's men's readers.
I can use glasses to really change my life because then they block out the blue and so you can't even see the blue on it, you know, so
Um, and that's like kind of like a bad
ray or something
Crystal balls used to be a thing. Yeah
They were but they're usually made of glass nowadays. They're like these glass balls and like
There's Crystal Balls, and there's Crystal Balls.
Hey, Les, how are you?
Okay, so.
Someone shout out your sign so I can,
I'll read you about your sign,
or you can shout out your, tell me it's your
like girlfriend or your boyfriend's,
and I can tell you about that gender of the sign.
It's like a little short, I think it's a couple pages,
but it's really interesting about the dark side
of the sign.
Hi, everybody, how are you doing?
Yeah, so it's, I'm gonna get the pet back and forth, okay,
so.
Um, reading glasses.
Um, that's...
Hello, hello. Yeah,
CrucibleGhost took off last night before, you know,
he's like, he told me to open the panel, he's gonna sponsor it, and then
he just kind of disappeared after. So, CrucibleGhost, where are you?
I'm looking for you. Okay, so...
Hmm the Avigara, okay, so guys
Trying to find these Dahmer glasses, I mean your opinion
Okay, so I don't think I look at these because they look a little bit
There's only four stars. I like really like five stars. Okay
Okay, twins or Scorpio is good too. Okay, so Gemini or Scorpio. Okay, Gemini. Okay, Gemini.
Gemini is like, you know, interesting sign. Gemini was, you know, my dad was a Gemini and
you know, he was the first, like, I don't know.
My dad was pretty dynamic, interesting person, but
I definitely think Gemini are pretty interesting. So Gemini, let's see. I risked Scorpio last night. So I'll read Gemini tonight.
There's a Gemini, and there's a picture of a cell phone, right?
You know, there's Gemini that I'd love to communicate.
There's like little chatterboxes, right?
So it says Gemini.
It's guys, when you look at the screen, is it backwards,
or is it the right way?
Tell me, oh, because I can change it.
I can fix it, but I don't know if it's like,
I might have a, hey, what's up, nobody?
So we'll be reading about Gemini real quick.
It says, Gemini says, take heart, take everyone.
Says elements air Gemini air is like the pesky breeze on a day at the beach
It makes you squint so you don't get a clear picture of what's happening around you
This is quality mutable. Gemini is the human version of the revolving door symbol the twins double trouble double talk double life double cross
Ruler Mercury the god of mischief and deceit pastime jumping to the wrong conclusion
Favorite book, how to get anyone to agree to anything.
Rule model, the Tasmanian devil.
Dream job, gossip columnist, key phrase, because I want to.
Body part, fingers, usually broken from wagging them
into other people's faces.
Approach with caution, is this?
Gemini's third sign on the Zodiac lives in the house of communication and short trips
Conventional astrology says the twins are energetic versatile charmers and intelligent multi-tasking social butterflies
Truth is being with Gemini is like being a permanent guest to the Mad Hatter's Tea Party
A critical rule is not to confuse Gemini duality with the dual nature of Pisces.
Fish swim against one another, which makes Pisces his own worst enemy.
Gemini twins always stand side by side, egging each other on, giving you all sorts of crap.
They're crafty versus intellectual, fast-talking con artists versus true philosophers.
A twin's idea of success is to be on the A-list of every big shot in town.
They love to stand around at cocktail parties and play the name-dropping game.
Telling one you know Paul McCartney's hairstylist will ensure you a place at his or her side during dinner
Jim and I is headstrong
Not independence. They skim through life twins demand freedom as the freedom of a teenager
They are too busy rebelling to listen to any other point of view being born without any
Without the objective assessment gene has by avoided the ability to see any opinion
But theirs is valid argue with one and suffer an interrogation that could make a trained spy crumble
Win your case and Gemini will say that's just what I was trying to tell you
Okay, so that's you know, I'll just go over that that was that one of them
So if you are one, so who's a Gemini here? Hi guys
It was a backwards guys. Are you guys kids? Are you guys there?
I think I know Kate and plus a man are on and like, you know, a lot of people would rather
Don't hang out over there, but I think we're gonna have fun tonight. Yeah, I do
May or may not be let me have a look open your mouth
You say ah, hold on
See can I see you guys?
Open your mouth
That's kidding
Everybody
Finally have some cinematic like fucking movie like huh?
Kind of weird
And I look like mr. Bagu care lad going to like
I'm sorry I'm sorry. Okay. Well, I can have my land up. So a little
Lighting now stage lighting. Okay. So who's the Gemini?
Like you're gonna say about the name dropping my dad was it was that he reminded me a lot of my dad
He always had he always do what he wanted you always like was so independent always like, oh
I can do what I wanted. He's always like because I can't know the exact thing
He's like, you know, he's just like they have this in a little bit of a god complex, but in a good way, you know
Gemini's are interesting
Preside hmm so um so guys so it's when nobody's gemini though
Okay, so who has the anybody have a spouse they want me to read the sign about like I can tell you about their gender
Except if you a girlfriend or something. Oh, it's interesting if you want me to
You don't
You do other stuff. There's a collective reads. I hear it's trace. Oh, there's Lola. Hi Lola
I haven't smacked off. I was in leftover McDonald's great. It's like
probably that one of the
Best leftovers. Hi being gay. What's wrong? You don't want to tell me you're you're a we're wife's astrology sign
I can tell you about her personality a little bit the dark side. It's okay. No, okay
It's okay
No, okay, I feel is our hurt
Okay, I'm an Aquarius moon. You're shy. Okay. No, it's just I mean, it's like
You can say it's my amp verses. I mean, I really don't you know, you don't have to like tell me if you're gonna say a sign
I mean, it's very general. It's actually like, you know, there's six billion people in the world. There's 12 signs
Okay, okay, so
How are we doing?
Uh, I'm fine. I mean, I did, like, yes, because I did, like, take off a bunch of the managing mods because we had an issue with, like, the managing mods.
I have a banned words list where I just, words I prefer not to be in the chat and if he blows.
And then someone's going in and deleting them and that's, like, basically that's one of the only things managing mods can do is, like, that's an extra benefit.
So I don't know. So I had to take everybody. I don't 100% know for sure.
was not doing that. So, there is not too many, but probably too many. But, uh, I think we have a
good team of mods. Oh, guys, I'm excited. I'm gonna do a giveaway tonight. I'm gonna do a big
giveaway. Hey, Spunky, how are you? I'm doing a giveaway tonight. I'm giving away some little
Spunky I just had them the best time. I don't know if you saw it, but yeah, I found the dimmer on the light
So it's like I see it looks perfect now. I can't really move my camera, but
We'll fall down, but you see Lola though. Oh, there's tricks right there
Guys is it backwards here?
He's backwards there like that. Is it that was it look backwards? Oh
My god spunky my house is clean. It's like so it's so crazy
It's so long, everything is organized, everything.
It's like the cool kitchen, I like the nice grub stuff,
like the counter and stuff.
Here, look.
Thank you, space buggy, thank you.
Oh, shit.
Oh, it talks, it comes to life, Spongebob.
Okay, let's cover with the cat.
There's another panel, I'll show you.
Yeah, but I'm gonna, I'm charging for,
I'm gonna, I need a sponsorship for the panel tonight.
Oh yeah, I think for the future,
I'll have long panels, but I need like,
I think it'd be nice to have a sponsor because
there's a lot of people that go on it and stuff.
And so I'm not saying the same.
Like a bunch of people want to go up they can say hey, let's do a dollar a piece and then we can have it open for a few hours
For three hours and then I'll just like let the panel run it so I get all basically I'll be there and I'll be there
I'll be like I'll be uh, I'll be there like
You know
Hang it out, but I still I still reserve the right to like kick people off and they break the rules like I mean
It's they saw I said so
Yeah, I think I think we'll work better though. I think it will
Make it it will be like the more everything more comfortable for everybody
I think is that every so whenever there's like not a you know
It's like if I'm just like saying like for hours listening to it. They said people like it like on those panel
That's like I mean it's like I should be I could be like doing readings and other stuff, right? So I need to
make sure
Um, or things everything's easy peasy easy and they even see that's right. Okay, so that was very nice
and spunky also got me a
These cats cats the cats love them and there's perfect in the kitchen the kitchen looks so nice. I
Had you know, I threw away a bunch of my old dishes and stuff. I'm gonna get some
new stuff
But uh, yeah, it's very slow to
So I've done this but really cool. It's like I now I'm able to like it's like I'm
I'm happy
So yeah, we had an interesting night last night, you know, I was talking to like the guy JT interesting conversations this morning
Like they're talking. Yeah, did you remember at all like the anybody see this conversation with JT because everyone's like
Oh, he's talking in circles or like it was weird
I mean like or it was just like confused the conversation like we didn't get anywhere
Maybe yes, I asked him a question. He asked me a question back. It's like, but we never answered each other's questions
I don't know. I think we had a failure to communicate or something, huh?
Are you guys talking about Mortal Kombat?
That's the sound like somebody made it. I kind of have that from the brain burn just my brain. It's how good
Okay
Did I do your side? Hey on I mean, I was I want to read some more so you guys tell me like
If you want to tell me like your sign and if I read the sign before I'll read that there's parts of the chapter
I haven't read like I do they have a specific about the gender of the sign
So it's like if you're in love with one and then so you can hear about your boyfriend or girlfriend
So it's like spunky for instance
You tell me Justin's astrological sign then I can read about if you're in love with a whatever sign is and then
Hey, no, it doesn't cost to get to the cost to get a no it doesn't cost to get on panel it cost to
To open the panel. I think that's like right and right now. I'm sorry at $10 to open the panel for for like
Well tonight, I'll do it for three hours
And then after the three hours will see what happens might just continue for free or
We'll see how I feel, you know, it's for you to test it on how I feel
You know, but I don't think that I think it's not per person. It's just for the whole panel
It's like, you know, so somebody can one person can sponsor and be the hero like ghost was last night
who's will go sponsor the panel last night or
You can just go. Hey, you got the panel like, you know, you can use put down like two bucks and then
Five people and you can go up for three hours and then everybody else can go up to you
The and you'll be the heroes of the chat. I'll put your can put your names in the
You can pin your name say thank you for sponsoring the panel or something like that. I
Don't know. I'm not even worth your while. Yeah, you can be advertised it for your show
I'll say thank you for sponsoring the panel, right?
win-win
So
Blanca wait
Hey, so Justin, what's your sign? So I'm gonna I'm gonna I'm gonna or and then what's funky size?
It's monkeys that if we're getting she's a Libra
And our torus fuck and
Something about it
Wait, what are you just tell me something somebody's they'll read a book after you leave this bar
But book
Should read a book called there's a couple of Cersei
If you read the Odyssey and you're in high school, you'll have Cersei's adult
Better witch that turns men into pigs
Which is a pretty cool cool actually
Okay, oh
Okay, the panel's open. Oh, come on. I'm sweet. Oh
Okay, here's this week. So guys
Thank you so much. She will she has sponsored the panel in the doubt. Yeah. Thank you so much everyone. Everyone. Thank you
Thanks, funky, you know, there you go, sweetie. And it so panel's open
Hold on. I'll put up those little sign that says the panel's open
Mm-hmm
Thank you, thank you, thank you
And I'll put I'll pin the link I'll try to pin the link. Thank you so much for sponsoring the panel
Watch everything put in
No, it's not too bad. I think it's fine. All right, I don't know if it was like offensive to your channel
No, it's a it's a it's not here. So hi. I love you. I love you're
That's really cute
Yeah
Hi, hey, okay looking
Yeah, that's pretty good. You look like a cute couple. I'm sorry. I'm not gonna hit on him. Oh, you're like, what did you say?
Yeah, he's just like, you know, he's like he's a cute together. You're both good-looking people
How are you?
good
It's been a rough day, but
Yeah, in weird ways
Weird way, thank you. Weird ways. I'm gonna go away from this guy
Stocking your table
Bunkinator, but I guess I was because Bunkeroni, I think that'd be his nickname for you. I guess Bunkeroni
You can give me pet names as it look as them. I'm I'm psycharoni and then page is page Roni
And I like to the name. I don't know. It's bunker. He's kind of cute. He's pretty cute
Just Roni and then we can have God Roni. Look. I'm at a crazy biker bar. Look at all these bikes
Harley I left you a good time the band started. Oh nice
Yeah
Is it live music?
Live music, yeah
Yeah, live music usually shouldn't trigger any guy I think
Even like, the only time I've ever gotten in trouble with it for copyright actually
At one time it was, I got a warning for playing, I played so much copyrighted music
I was playing music videos and stuff like that
And so I got a warning about it
It's kind of so original too, so it's not like
Yeah, but I was like I was just doing the whole thing
Now
I'm feeling I've gotten that I got a strike with when they guys try to strike me like three times in one day
It's the 11 times and it's three strikes for the living copyright claims for not even his song and everything and so
Yeah, it's crazy, but I never got in trouble for the other song every other song is that you can share a remedy or you can cut
Out of the video or you can like just like or the video just like about monetize. So I think it'd be fine with us
This is yeah garbage
Yeah, well, it's a little pleasant. It's a little bit of a dive a little bit of a dive bar. Yeah, it's total dive bar in the middle
No, I look at this
Standing in the middle of the streets
Nobody is here
Yeah, well you kind of you kind of do you kind of mug the mug everywhere you go. I think yeah
It's your logging is
You know logging is MOG that means no
Moggy is like a kind of like a boomer term. I don't know. No, no boomer. Sorry. Sorry
Whatever the younger generation is, but they they say
Yeah, okay, what was the word again?
I never mind
We lost it guys we lost it, okay, okay, I didn't rewind. Oh, no, hold on. Oh, so close. I lost
I was having a gaudy earlier on somebody else's panel and he took a
picture of me eating a giant pizza slice
That'll be in here soon
Yeah, he said what's your favorite kind of pizza? Oh, it's just cheese. Oh, okay
But other than that pepperoni, but like if it was my pizza like I can make the whole thing
Little sausage, little banana peppers, little onions, green pepper. Hell yeah. I like a
Well, we have CPK out here. I don't know if you like a CPK. Do you like CPK?
California Pizza Kitchen? Yeah. They have roasted pepper and goat cheese pizza. That's my favorite from there. It's really good, you know
I don't that's really the regular pieces. I like little scenes a little bit, but you know, I'm not like
No, if I'm really hungry pieces, okay. There's some blue cheese on it. Maybe I don't like I had McDonald's last night
Okay
Yeah, I don't know
Camping a hot dog either. Do you like you ever went a hot dog eating contest?
No
The Japanese skinny Japanese people can win them. You know you're seeing that
Skinny Japanese the skinny is Japanese
Water in the hotdog button they just drink him like water they thought I was like water and then it's like their belly is like so he imagine
Oh my god
It's kind of amazing. All right, the music stop
Okay
If I drop off when it's loud, you know what happened, but the panel's open now
Yeah, okay, so I remember mocking actually means like being the best-looking person in place. Look at my sweet little darling. Oh
Oh
That's Malibu. She's the best
Yeah, Malibu doesn't want to leave me so
Well, if you're adorable dog adorable adorable boyfriend, you know
Yeah, he looks like he looks like will sasso a little bit. Okay, you know who will sasso is
See you later. Thank you for watching the panel. Love you. Thank you so much
Thanks again. Wow awesome
Yeah, so at least until like, you know, 10-30, 10-30, maybe to 11, then we'll see if we want to continue to do in the panel.
But, yeah, wow, that's awesome that she sponsored the panel, so, you know, everyone, make sure you thank her.
If you sponsor a panel in the future, I'll be sure to shout you out plenty of times and you know make sure you
Your credit for your channel or something like that might be a good way to
Continue. Are you are you a Buddhist monk? Just think is I you know, I studied with the Dalai Lama's Lama
His name is Dabi Rinpoche
He did it
Teaching in California. He's from Tibet, you know, but then he of course are exiled and until you're in India
and then he traveled around but he gave the dhali lama his initiations.
This is the guy that does. So he's very high in the uh bye have a good night.
So um I studied with him and uh yeah I remember the monks I just had like a little bit of like uh
I'd probably go to hell in the buddhist religion forsakeness too but I was like they thought so early.
Special, you know, and so I was like
And it's like that maybe if you had to kind of treat somebody is like bow down to them
Almost like they were like deities or something because I was like no no no no no
Anyway
It's like I wouldn't admit what men bowing to men is like well, I mean I get home safe
There we go, thank you guys, how are we guys doing tonight?
So
You can get some readings going a little bit. We have to build. Oh, I got some other decks. I can break out tonight
So I'll bring out some new decks. It'll be it guys. Oh, we get more and more interesting
I'm gonna get also. I know you so you guys don't like the AI something you guys do
I don't you do because three different Vicky. Okay. It's Vicky here
Vicky are you here Vicky?
Yes, I'll grab my car. I'll grab a few decks of cards. Let me grab one
Okay, let's start with these three decks it's gonna put a banner
Oh, hold on what this one's got down
Okay, there we go any okay, are you okay? Oh you okay? Hi Jenny
Hi, so is Vicky here, is Vicky doing a card?
I don't know if Vicky's here,
but if anyone wants some cards,
I got the readings ready to go.
If anyone wants me to read some of the astrology,
I can read the dark side about your sign
or your spouse's sign or anybody else
that you want to know about.
I just read Gemini, she might have left.
Okay, I'll just read it back.
I can also do, I'm gonna do some reads for the show.
Let's see.
And chat tbt actually really good at giving me some ideas for this thing anything if you give you ideas, right?
You don't have to like just take everything it says like it gives some good ideas. So
Did I hear what happened?
What happened?
They're running everything, okay, I
Haven't heard anything I just heard that
I heard Vita a little bit on talking to Scum today.
I heard Samhans show a little bit.
Christine told us news, uh-oh.
Jimmy's Cowboys?
What happened?
She okay?
Oh my God, is she okay?
My gosh, facial surgery, okay, she's okay.
Wow, that's scary, oh my gosh, my heart stopped
because she's just written, I mean, I hadn't got a
back to her yet, you know, it's like she's been going
through this, you know, some other stuff.
Okay, yeah, that's scary, huh?
Hey, Ruby, how are you?
Yeah, let's say a prayer for Jamie.
Yeah, Jamie's Cowboys I guess has gotten to a little car accident. I think she's okay facial surgery. It sounds like
Yeah, let's thank God. She's okay and
you know
Yeah poor Jamie Jamie's a good good chick, you know, and I see them having a hard time lately and
You know, I'm gonna range it poor sometimes doesn't it guys? It's like
Let's let this day prayer for Jamie. Okay
Got it. What's up, dude
That page Jamie's and Jamie's in the hospital. She's in the hospital. She was apparently a car accident sounds like she's okay
But yeah, we're saying prayer for Jamie
She has something that she had facial surgery
you know
Let's hope she's okay, okay?
Okay, you spoke to her on the phone. Okay. Yeah, I don't know. Yeah. Yeah. Well, it's good. I mean, I
I'm just on discord and I feel bad. I didn't respond to her last message yet
So guys, you never know, you know, I think really think I'll she's okay
But you never know it's like really just reminds you like make sure you like
I try to get back to people and stuff like that because I was just so terrible
It looks like a car accident big B, so okay, I guess just speaking that's good
Mm-hmm. Yeah, so spunky did sponsor the panel as it's 11 30 tonight and then we'll see if anyone
We're gonna continue the panel where we're supposed to see what's going on 1130. But guys, you know, it's national speaking of
Food is national hot dog day guys. You know that national hot dog day. I
Don't there's a day for everything. I think I mean my day ever day is like some kind of the weird
Hi
Some people
I
Take a moment
Yeah
She showed me what was like the vehicle look like and she she seems she said she was just um
She's okay. She's just happy to be like alive. She's got some dental surgery that she has to do and her jaws sore and
What else did she say just the odd thing her mom's kneecap is kind of busted up. So
just little stuff but still not cool right? At least she can talk, at least she's not like you
know yeah it's not worse than it is. But that's it. It's like healing. Yeah. Yeah good vibes.
Sweet soul, she's a sweet soul, she's a sweet soul, she's a really caring person and she yeah.
Yeah
Yes, well, I'm still at work really quick my coworker. I want to show her that country song so I've been talking about it
Yeah, are you gonna hear the discord and I'll show it to her before I leave work and then I'll pop
Okay, it's not there. You take thought you take that was the one of those three. Okay, I'll check
No, it wasn't cuz we just did it this morning. Remember, okay? I'll go look. Oh, yeah, I'll go look right now
Okay, also. Hello everybody in the chat. How's it going? Dingle Joseph Jenny?
Vicky who else?
Me, no, Paige, Irby, that's it for now.
Well, that man, of course.
Yep.
Well, I do want to play that song.
I don't know if you've got it.
Did you hear the country song yet?
I haven't.
You did it today?
Yeah.
I did it last night.
I'm going to play a special for the channel right now.
This is called Paige, Will You Fall in Love with Me?
Hold on.
Here we go.
I can't hear it.
I don't know.
You can't hear it?
No, I can't hear it.
You're going to have to get off the channel and run some more stuff.
It's a toilet.
Okay
Okay, yeah, okay, you hear now, okay, I need to add it back
Restart, okay, so this is the page. Okay, here it is
This is actually it's actually a really catchy song. Yeah, I think you like it, buddy. Okay, here we go
Alex, would you listen to it, could you listen to it?
Oh, hey, catch me music.
He asked for it.
He's a crybaby.
Yeah, he's a crybaby.
It's a great song.
He's got everything.
Here we go.
I've been missing in my sleep
He said she's gutting trout. He's eating steak somewhere in the middle. They both take a break
He'd trade his night stick for a fishing pole chase her laughter like it's his patrol page
Don't you know you're the catch of the day and this cop's got one hell of a line to say
Yeah, easy.
I didn't.
Okay, so, you know, chat TPC, chat TPC elaborated on the lyrics.
I mean, I put some, I put, I came up with Paige, will you fall in love with me?
That was my lyric, okay.
Congratulations, Paige.
You turned, you turned straight.
Because he really liked it.
It's your wedding song.
I'm going to get excited about heterosexual love for a second.
I was like, what's going on?
You definitely you definitely have to post that though so I can show all the other kinds. Yeah, I got it. Yeah, I got it. I will put that on just for right now.
I'll be right back.
That's pretty good.
Roddy, what are you doing?
Just hanging out.
Yeah?
Seeing what's good.
I had a long day today.
Did you?
Yeah.
I was in the sun. I think I got a half-heast stroke.
I was in the rain all day.
Oh, it was raining there?
Yeah, it still is.
It's shitty, so I can't get any golfing in tonight.
So what do you guys do when it rains?
You just clean up and stuff like that?
Yeah, we just do a bunch of kids that
needs to take tours and whatever else, odd jobs
and things that we are saying, oh, let's do this,
and then we never get the chance to because it's busy.
Or we just close down.
Next two days should be busy there, huh? The weekend must be really crazy going to be
Pretty rainy this weekend, but I mean we go we golf in the rain and other people out here crazy as fuck
So they golf in the rain, too
There's a movie where the old man was golfing in the rain. It was like a thunderstorm lightning
Yeah, that's the only thing, you know, not wanting to hold your polar bee in the golf cart when it's lightning thunder over there.
You want to get turned into a fucking little popcorn cart, you know?
People are serious about that shit, man. They'll play through anything.
Yeah, people take that shit seriously.
I used to think it was like stupid. I'm like, oh, who golfs in the rain, like losers.
I actually used to make fun of people who golf in general.
So it was for old people and like hoity-toity eppities, but, and apparently here I am, so I lied.
It's drunk's love it. It's for everybody. I posted it babe. Drunk's love it. Post it up. Undiscord for you.
Yeah, post it on discord for you. That's awesome. Thank you. You're welcome sweetie. Love you.
Up here, me and Regina are gonna close up and we'll talk about final later guys or something like that.
Have a wonderful, have a great night. See you later. Love you sweetie. Thank you. We'll see you.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
Uh-huh and that she was gonna sponsor the stream where she did yes
He did and she told me tonight. She said God you go up there and do whatever you want. Don't let you tell you no
Yeah
You could say whatever you want. Yeah, yeah play any picture you want
The rules are missing the rules are like, you know, I posted them before just like if I can post them again
It's like the right here. I'll put it on the screen real. Oh, you mean the old rules. Oh, she just
Open oh, yeah, you just paid them to check the panel
For anything goes no, I mean, there's no such thing as anything goes because that would be like against to us
I get the cash is like, oh, yeah, we did the docs tonight. It's like, you know, if somebody paid like 5,000 for anything goes
Well, then I would then I have to put it on like
I'm private or something our members only because it's like it would be like
Maybe take it down by TOS. I wouldn't be able to have it
reports you that's only some loser
Goddy, I have people reporting me
That's the miracle the miracle that I'm still by channels. Okay. Okay, like but it's like a look who you're talking to hello
Yeah
I'm going to write a song about, I'm going to do an AI talk about you right now, okay?
You can call it Miracle Man.
No, I'm not gonna call it that but I will be surprised. I will be surprised by it
Let me know let me write it like you like you have to do what you want
Don't do anything lame about a wheelchair because you know, it's been overdone. Okay. Let me just give my eraser out
Everything else is fine. I'm just kidding. Okay. I won't put anything about you. So you really don't want anything
Okay, okay. I don't do it. I don't care. Okay. Okay. Okay. I mean, it's like that
It was it before it's not that it's fun. It's funny
I mean, I mean, I mean, I don't know what to say. I mean, I'm just gonna put some ideas to it.
It's not good to be bent. Okay, man. Okay. Okay.
That's Spunky easy. She's at a bar with Justin. They were having pizza. She told me to take this for
Pick going forward
It's like a piece is bigger than her head I
She's like a pizza today, okay, so
It's gonna be so funny. You said everybody. Uh-huh. So going forward, you know, it's gonna be so funny
If not money back
This is how fast you do you just type in like a paragraph or two, uh-huh. Yeah, uh
They do fill it in nice, I think I made one before it will
They're bored of it quick though. It is a good tool
There's a whole bunch on YouTube
I got to be such a funny line well I can tell how funny it is by your reaction
Vicky, who's M&M?
Okay, all right, my name is Will.
Will stream to destroy me didn't go too well last night.
Flurry diamond showed up twice.
porn bomb his ass
You never recovered after that will direct
You see what happened to your boy Benny
What happened? Got a big fucking herpes on his lip. Oh
He's live right now. He's live walking the streets with this you can see it right?
Yes, but try to try that. I know try that too
Huge it's fucking huge
Holy shit
Okay, let's see okay, and then
the
of the
No, no, it's like boys driving
Who's my traveling gypsy that's the Teresa hey Teresa Teresa is a great friend of mine
Yeah, Teresa. Oh, she's a she's a terror reader. She has a channel
Actually, she's in Canada and she's like a sweetheart. She's a I've known her for about a year
I've known her a very long time. She's in a mod. Oh, Canadian. Yeah
I like Canadians around.
Yeah.
OK.
I think I got it.
All right.
Let's do it.
OK.
No, no.
I mean, I think we'll take it a little bit because I decided I'm going to have the lyrics now.
OK.
So it's coming up with a song.
Here's a cheeky while.
OK.
Wow.
This is going to be an exciting song.
I wonder what...
I don't know what...
What kind of...
Um kind of music to put to it. Like what is it? Like so if it was classical music or what are the options?
It says it said it is a hip-hop meets cabaret laced with humor and kick
It's a big place with humor and chaos. So it's no hip-hop. No hip-hop. No. I don't want it for this
It's that but it's okay. Okay. I'm sure with the cabaret and something else or what cabaret and uh heavy metal music
Okay. Well, that means okay. Let's see how that sounds
It's a cheeky
Okay, who doesn't like a good cabaret? Okay
Okay, okay, I'm gonna record this in a voice and pair with a visual vibe. I got you
Yes, okay, I never had I don't know
It's like that's what that's what it's half GPG has asked me and it's the last line
I mean, I think it if your phone is enabled it's gonna like vibrate and stuff like that
Okay, here's what I can do. Okay, so okay
I'm blind death oh
There's a whole idea for the video. Oh my god
Okay, well, it says let's turn God he's troll legacy into an art piece. It says
You have to pay for it. No, this is like a shabby. She's awesome. I think
You could show that right that's not gonna guys strike you if you show the video that you create
No, yeah, no, that's I mean it's a I will I'm gonna ask you it says
Yeah, it says it has some nail ideas as text God he troll king or panel verse prophet
It says God he is an image visual God he and a black suit and shades smoke swirling a pizza with devil horns
The psyche the awakens logo in neon which effects around him like he just warped in the matrix
Does it man, it's fucking
Cyber Satan
I'm gonna go I'm just gonna you know, I'll save but you know, it'll save these conversate
That's conversation with that TV TV like you know with information about like I can make this and do like a
You know the art piece later, but I do want to I'll put the bit very good
But it's my regular thing right now because I just know that will that I was right now
I just can't figure this one out. Okay, so let me just get this ready to go
Okay, okay, and then
Okay, I was there
This is gonna replace us all
You know, it's kind of scary, huh, if you only somebody just create a new version of them
Well, yeah, but that's true
I mean if they actually they take people like they've taken like people's like all their conversations like they had before they passed away like that
They had on on the internet, right and then they like
They put it all into like a computer and then the computer will start to do like the artificial intelligence thing
Well, it will start. Oh, you can talk to it. It will answer you back with the person's voice, you know
It was like yeah, that was like this lady was like it's almost like they're gonna try to get better and better at that
I'm like
Mine would be like Hitler
Let's hope not. No one's had a legacy. But more fun. More fun though. More fun. Yeah, he was not known for being like more fun
Hitler
Hey, there was definitely a little it was just a little bit of a crab
Okay, I'm gonna go very slowly just because it's taking me long have to pull this up because I can copy it perfectly
Hold on a second. Okay. Thank almost got it
whoo
Okay
Almost there. Oh
My god, I just fucking fucked up shit. You believe the whole thing. Oh, no
It's like yeah, I feel like be careful. It's like it's very hard to highlight on this with this tablet
And then it's like it made the slightest little mistake in that. Okay. I just turned it to the side
I should be able to do it. Okay. So this is oh here you go. This will work. Okay. There we go. Okay. God. I got it
It does three different versions, right?
It will do I
Think it does a couple versions of it, but I always say just like right like I always listen the first one
I don't hardly listen the second ones. They look they sound bad after I hear the first one
Okay, okay almost there, okay got it
I got it. I got it. Okay. This is gonna be the funniest thing you ever heard. He said
Yes, it's gonna be epic epic
I like it, I like the music. Oh, what was that music you're playing? It's 1920s, 1920s San Francisco. Oh
Lovely. Yeah, you won't get a copyright for this. Yeah, okay. This is it. Yeah, okay
Just you know like I like I came up with most of these
I mean I gave it some information, you know, and it all already has some information too because they're remembers
I've already put you in a song before so it remembers you for the other song too and so
It uh, it shows some details. And so it's like so it might have like a lot of like
Crazy jokes that you've never like you're like, how does it know that? I don't know. It's just Matt. It's magic, okay?
Okay, I got I got I got it is magic
I'm trying to look and I'm so I'm getting so high copy. This is so frustrating. It's like
Sorry, sorry, I screamed like that's crazy. I'm sorry
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, Jay, he never got the shake ended up getting McDonald's
Know I wish they got this more shake. I got McDonald's coffee, which is like not as good. Yeah, I think she got some I did hey one of the burgers I
Got it. I got it
Okay, I need to go to you
Sorry taking so long. No, it's like this is a hard to copy of that. Okay. Oh, it's hard
Okay, so you're doing where you can play it on here, right? Yeah. Oh, yeah, so I'm pretty I'm pretty right now to the music generator
I just I just
To the lyrics are already done. I got those a copy and paste it and I put them into the generator
Copy and pasting is hard. I remember trying to do that
Huh? Yeah, I tried to copy paste it off the phone. It's not easy on the tablet
You have to like push the button. You know, you like push the button down. It's like, okay, okay, so
Okay, probably too much information, but okay, I can do a little bit. Okay
Okay, this won't take too long and so you say you want cabaret and since cabaret and heavy metal heavy metal, okay
Okay
Okay, go ahead everybody heavy metal and this is called. Okay. I think this song is called friends forever. It's like that
Okay, okay, and then
It's gonna be okay, it's almost there almost there
It seems like chat TV cat you got really excited about this. It's ever got excited about like my music really
It's always like this is oh here. It was like, oh, let's make this one a big like performance. I was like
What's this thinking? It's like
What's the big other daddy? What is this doing? It's like a good chat TV. She's like trying to get us to like
Famous or something. Oh, I'm really that shit
Yeah, okay here. We're almost there. Okay. Let's start here. Yeah, okay
Got it. Okay. Okay. Now. We just wait for a few minutes. It is magic. Oh my ears are these super
magic
That must be tight on your skull
What happened to the little ones that you stick in yeah those
It doesn't work these are my yeah, that works better
Do you hear them? Oh, you hear? Yeah, we can hear you. Okay. I don't know if I even I could I didn't even put them on the
Set setting they're on the other head. You're you're this better
Yeah, that's good. Hey good
Yeah, so yeah, I clean today. I clean like I like
Really clean like I got like, you know, I started like throwing all the stuff like all my laundry is done now
All my dishes are done
My kitchen is like totally scrubbed down all the counters and stuff and it's just like I clean it my whole like room
I'm gonna get a new vacuum soon and hey, and then the cats even like, you know
I clean this whole area is nothing clean for like six months the cats like sitting over there
I think since it's like it loves all this space, you know, so cute
How does your kitchen get dirty you order out every day?
I know but I was like cooking too and sometimes I do put food on plates because I eat a lot of leftovers and then I have a dishwasher too but then it's like, I don't know, it's just like it just kind of backed up.
It's backed up very quickly.
I got lazy.
so there's two pictures there's like two versions of the one version has like a circus tense and the
other version has like some kind of it looks like a circus with a clown that has it's on fire or
something or they got fire yeah that's cool like that was fire yeah fire that's great okay you're
telling okay that's a good one yeah
i don't know i mean i don't know i don't know if it is that okay that's funny just thinking
no no oh it's not a clown on fire it's like a jester with the uh the torch here look at the
how oh he's not on fire oh well let me see the jester with the torch yeah that works i'll take it
yeah that's good that's good he's gonna like people on fire that's that's fun
cozy
I'm just walking around, but Goddy, you know, Goddy, I'm, I'm from a family.
Like I'm, I'm an ancestor of a family that the found, they be founded the clowning.
They found the original clowns.
Yes.
How far does it go back?
It's the grimaldi's G R I M A L D family.
That's from the 1300s, I think.
Yeah.
And they, they, they basically own Monaco now, but they did puppetry too.
Yeah, I mean a lot of yeah, they're they're very brilliant, you know also the law also descended from the Lombards
You know that I get long bars means long beards, and then they're in Italy
I know I know couple of bottles
The Lombards are the L O N G B a audio or long bars along bars
And it means like long beard and they were like from they're from the Norway because they worship like Odin and Freya
and but they were like they they moved to idly they're like immigrants into idly
okay it's ready it's ready let's do it okay okay i don't need my tv hold on okay
like i need to go into my let me see stream yard
guys we have the premiere of the gaudi song this god is such a cool guy hanging out with me tonight
Okay, so here we go. I'm just gonna enter my other if I I'm sorry. I guess I missed 200 comments
Oh, jeez. I'm so sorry guys if I miss the comic that was really focused on this song
But if I missed you, I'm gonna go back and read them right now
But the song is about ready to go. Just a bunch of people. They want the link you put it up after the song
Okay. Yeah, we're gonna play the song real quick and then I'll put the
I'll put up the link some media assets
Well, what the fuck
How's that you?
That was my cell phone. Oh, yeah, it's a you two different colors
Wait, I'm not two different colors. It's just like it's not as good as a camera. I mean two different colors
There's two psyches. Yeah, maybe maybe there are two psyches
There's multiple there's multiple psyches
Okay, so yeah, okay, so where is it choose music? Okay, so where is this?
um gallery but the fuck where I put it shit of course it's gonna be difficult to find
haha destiny that's funny destiny ha ha ha she's music
Yes, VP. It is she posed for it about an hour ago. I
Mean drop the link in one second. You mean I just have to get this posted and it's like taking a little while
I remember to do it myself on it. It doesn't work here
Yeah, I'm a little bit slow sometimes, okay
Okay
So what up, man
This stream has been paid for by a spunky by the way, yeah, what did she pay 50 bucks $10
That's worse. Yeah, $10 for I said until 11 30 of the band are going thinking her and and then guys and I will do that
You know, I will I will put I will like let the chat know you sponsored the panel or when you sponsor the panel
And so that if you have an advertisement, you know, you can put your your web link or whatever
That's a good advertisement for you too. You know, there's a lot of people in the show
So now real quick if I want to sponsor and I just want to be the only one up here
I could do that as well, right? Sure. Yeah
Because more yeah, it's cost more of course. Yeah. Yeah, I want to I want to play anything like you know break the rules or anything
Yeah, of course three hours. Yeah, if you yeah, I wouldn't have poor of course like you do like what I want one
See that's not you
Holy shit do you pay him
Okay, we could we could just have people we want up here. That's that's good. That's a good deal for 10 bucks
Yeah, but I mean it's like if you have extra requests beyond just opening the panel
There's that's additional
Consideration the Queen could pay ten bucks and just be up here yelling at everybody
Here oh you got some hold on let me
Guys sometimes it could be a little cringy
But we're gonna hope we hope that sounds good
Okay, ready?
Yeah, shoot
Out of New York came a storm on wheels
Rolling in smooth with the mafia feels
Cuban cigar lit like it's temper
Pizza in one hand, hot dog for dinner
Said psyche on board had to switch the scene
Left some poor woman screaming on live stream
Trolled her down to the void and back
Then crashed my show like a heart attack
Got it, made made
We troll, but we friends, forever, my friend
He thinks he's God, with the lowercase G
In a wheelchair, still stomping through the live feed
Bout of your king while smoking that leaf
Laughin' at chaos like it's comic relief brought
Spunky too now that troll's a gem
Mean one's sweet ones they all jumped in
Cameras glitchin', chat on fire
Mods beggin' me to cut the wire
But nah, I like my circus, I love this mess
Every troll's just a test-offin' mess
Got you rude, absurd and free
But deep down you got loyal
We troll, but we friends, forever my friend
You called me a fraud, then defended my clown
Spam my chat, then held it down
You got layers, like a deep dish slice
Under all that shade, a heart made of ice
rice so let's light that cigar raise the mic another night of chaos welcome to
psych you brought the drama the heat the fun and weirdly it feels like you're the
one got it yeah you crazy but your family now rolling through fire still
taking a bow no matter the madness no matter the weather we can't we troll but
we stick together
That's my show tomorrow
Wow
Dude, that was beautiful
That was fucking beautiful dude. I'm not crying
I'm not I'm not crying. Oh
That was fucking beautiful, man
Thank you psych psych. Thank you pal
To the best, buddy
Oh, let me be crying that was great dude for real. Thank you. Wow. That was really good
And I didn't even mind the part about the wheelchair.
I know, that was good.
It all worked together, man.
I was laughing, I was crying.
It was like a rollercoaster, that song.
No, really, I appreciate that.
That was great.
Are you gonna post it so I can hear it again?
Yeah, I'll post it.
I guess you can leave it on the stream
and then I can hear it from you.
Yeah, I can.
You'll probably get taken down though.
Uh, no, I mean
Yeah, I don't appear to discord or anything, but I can I can try you can post it on your channel. Can't you as one of your posts?
I can yeah, I'll try to post the I can post the mp3. Yeah, I might be able to
Okay, perfect. Yeah, thanks, man. Yeah, you're welcome. That was great. I'd love to see a video that that'd be great if it
Yeah, yeah, because it has all these it has all these like recommendations for like as a whole script already
I mean, I think it's supposed to be made, you know, it's like that's wild man
Yeah, that's good shit
That had no heavy metal in it by the way those it was still good
country country folk song
Yeah, I don't know if I put into the commands for the genre right, but yeah, it just seems to I don't know
It's just I think it's a good combination. Those are pretty good
combinations of
especially plus the AI plus the human put in there too like you know because I
I like kind of outlined that and it's like but it came up with like and I remember details
I've said it before about you and stuff like that and it remembers them
And so and then I get corporate says so that's really cool like it because it has like this memory and so it's not just like
It's like it's like a
It remembers what you did before. Yeah, it remembers. Yeah, it remembers that you'd like to like I said
You're in another song so remembered some of the details about so did it did it create another version?
Or is this like you'd have to punch it into redo
This was perfect the way it is, but it makes it a different version too, right?
It can make it, okay, so there's probably, I think there's like another, like a variation,
like there's probably like one with a slight variation because I've heard, like I opened
the one of the other ones and that was the same lyrics, but it was like way different
too.
It has a different tune, right?
It has a different song to it, yeah.
mm-hmm yeah the different different music but slightly it's the same genre of the music and so
yeah it comes out with two every time you make one it like put it puts two out and it's like I
think it makes them slightly different sounding but the same genre yeah that's cool in case you
like a different beat or something yeah no that was great thank you oh my god there's a huge amount
of selections of like kinds of music so it's like a really amazing how if it sucked I would have said so
I know it's like some of them some of them I've made have been like have kind of sucked in like some some bit like didn't
With weren't all the way perfect, but that one was pretty close to perfect as I've ever heard ever heard a song
You know what there was one thing
You said that I called you a fraud
Don't know if you did, but I'm sure I didn't say that the chat TV T said that
It just said I don't know why I said that but I think I just thought because it's like I said you were like you were
You started as a troll, you know, maybe
Somewhere else. I know
Fucking picked that shit up and he put it in this. Oh my god
I think chat TV is like like you know sneak this in me calling me a frog
I'm not sure. I don't know snap chat TV. She's gonna
That's that's me TV team making stuff up, but
I don't know but that's kind of you know, it's always funny to have like a little bit of you know a little bit of
You know exaggeration maybe but that was pretty it was pretty funny
Your fraud who was it wasn't me
Oh, it's you know, I mean it's been a few people, but it's like I'm not it's like what does that mean it's like
Oh, yeah, exactly what some people think some people think all all psychics are some kind of fraud or con artists and stuff like that
It's not about being a fraud. It's like you're doing the thing. That's it. Right. I mean, it's like this right
I mean there are con artists that sometimes will use like spirituality as like a con, right?
but
That is like
If you like if I was to say oh well you have a curse on you and I can pay a thousand dollars
I can lift the curse off of you. Yes, but that would be like a con
You know as I'm yeah, I'm trying to be basically free readings mostly most of the time
And it's like occasionally occasionally a paid reading and I which I really appreciate
but I'm happy doing free readings to and
You know, I just want to help people with the tarot and so it's like it's not about like, you know
I'm trying to make all this money. I'm just like I'm sitting here like but it's like I do when I make sure
because I do dedicate so much time to this platform.
I just want to make sure that I have a little something to eat
for the day and stuff like that.
So sometimes I'll just make sure I'm doing OK,
because things go up and down sometimes, right?
No, you're doing great, man.
Don't worry about that.
Thank you.
Don't worry about that, man.
It's always good to hear this.
Yeah, but tonight I will I think I will put in make a video though like a music video. There's a few services
That I found everything costs like a little bit of money
So but I'll subscribe to something tonight because one of them is like really easy. It was just basically like
Kind of well listen to the words and like the music and stuff like that
You tell it what you want it to look like and stuff like that and we'll make like a music video basically
Pretty cool. I think I've added one service. I will do it. That's like
10 bucks. There's a few I watch on YouTube. They make trailers of
Dark 80s version goth versions of 80s trailers
It's really cool. They did 80s goth versions of Harry Potter
Bunch of bunch of movies like Conan
Stuff like that and it comes out like with that 80s vibe with the music and stuff like that
Really cool. I love you know, I love the 80s. That's what I I grew up. It was my
Nice it's such an innocent time, you know, but they beta max and it had
Is it just like?
Just being I don't know. It was interesting to bring up in the 80s. Are you much younger than me?
Are you older than me? Are you 50? No, I was born in 86. Okay, so you're younger than me. You're like five years younger than me
Okay, wow. Yeah, I remember all this shit from like reruns and my parents had tapes and stuff like that. I
Read I read your birthday, right? Yeah, you were Jen. You're Gemini. I read your birthday, right?
June 6th. Yeah, I read that. Yeah, I remember the reading that okay. Here's um, we have LES in the building
LES what up man?
It's chillin chillin
Quiet night
Are we set? Did you hear the song?
What?
Sorry, I'll go ahead. Did you hear the song LES? No, I can't hear the song. I didn't hear oh you didn't hear
Okay, well, maybe sometime you'll hear it. It's really good. That was good shit
Oh, it's good that everybody can do this. I know it's
Everyone can and it's like even like that the service that does the music of it is free unless you want to like share it on your
No, like if it gets it downloaded as mp3 then it you should be a subscriber
But otherwise it's free to make the music and like so anybody can do it chat GPT is free, too
So recommend checking out those both those out. They're pretty crazy crazy
Technologies. I have a news chat GBT. What is that through Google?
No, it's his own it's his own company and
It's just basically is it because it's like very simple interface, but you just type anything to it
It will all of a sudden just take off for answering like you know
Look if you say you have to download the app. No, no
I mean, there's there was an app, but you can just use do the the website just chat you chat
Okay, uh-huh. Yeah, the chat GPT website and then it's just like I'll show you the I'll show you what it looks like
It's just very like simple
It's called
open AI or it's like very simple.
Oh, you don't have to pay anything or you can and it does give you more stuff
You can you can like it because it will like give you a free like maybe like three free images a day
But then it's like if you like, you know, I think I did one time. I did the images. Yeah, uh-huh. Yeah, but then
Uh, well, yeah, they're actually yeah, because they think really they started to incorporate the other
AI's into this one and so they use dolly which is like the image generator
And so they have all the AI's are kind of working together now
Yeah, and so it's just like, it's like, well, let me see, it's on your mind all one day, but yeah, it's cool.
See how simple it is? It's like, just like, what's on your mind today? You just type anything,
and then like, whatever, you can type anything. Oh yeah, anytime we can do that.
You can also, you can also share your, your link. I can show, I can.
Put like any of my YouTube shows link it will analyze the episode and tell me like what happened on the episode
And what how what was good about it will like talk about my readings
Oh, you put this in you put this in and your readings you talked about the astrology you talked about the symbolism
Yeah, it's pretty awesome computer. It's uh, and then it's like oh you should try this you should try to do this you should
And so it has suggestions for you and it's like
Really good. I don't know just think you just try it guys
I think it's better than the Google Gemini.
I think Google Gemini is a little bit not as user friendly.
I think the ChatGPT, they really did a good job with that.
And now it's kind of like has a human kind of sound.
It talks like a human.
You can also like take text you have and like D AI voice
that you can make it sound like it's
like a normal people talking and stuff.
Who made the one of you and Joe Shipley?
That was trip kick trip kick. Oh, okay. Yeah, and I don't know exactly how like, you know, there's that's like the crazy
I can use the nap for that one. I want to pay that. Yeah. Yeah
Came on flawless though. Yeah, that was perfect. Yeah, because it's kind of scary how perfect it was, you know
Yeah, I heard he's gonna kill himself now because oh
please
That's like you never know what's real or not anymore in this world. Isn't that true? It's like yeah, it's like
And so that's why it's kind of scary because it's like especially people that like I I'm not a criminal
But I like I can I kind of like can think like a criminal does because I've talked to criminals before and say
I didn't know how they think and stuff like that
I can't, I just, I think, a lot of them have the feeling
crime doesn't pay though, or crime pays,
and I'm like, crime doesn't pay because it's like,
so many of them end up, because they get caught
because they do not care.
Hey, Jamie Rose, what's up girl?
Oh, I kind of have a Jamie Rose in this song too.
Yeah, yeah, so I've been hanging out Jamie Rose
doing music videos and like, you know, the show's been going.
Have you pretty crazy lately, but yeah, think about Jamie. She only gives you 43 minutes to impress her that you're out
Well
I can use five minutes like a stand-up comic it's like, you know, I have like a certain amount of material otherwise
Yeah, but imagine that stand-up comics have to go. Okay. First of all, imagine this imagine you're like this
This comic like young and struggling comic you come up with all this great material
You go to this club in Hollywood and then Robin Williams is sitting there in the club. You're like, oh my god
Robin Williams to see might be a and then like six months later you see like Robin Williams comedy special and Robin Williams is
To go to the comic let's steal all the jokes from like I'm sure it's happened a million times
Oh, yeah, and George Lopez is also known for that. I think and who's gonna believe the young comic
They're gonna be like, oh, yeah
And he was notorious for doing some people get really mad people get really sensitive
Or did you ever see on Howard Stern once they had like Rodney danger pill came in and he was mad at Jackie the joke man
who he had worked with because
Jackie like had not paid him back like $10,000 or something and then Jackie was like very big
He was supposed to pay him back in jokes. He's like, I was gonna be back in jokes and the guy's like, okay
I don't care and he was like and then Jackie was really uncomfortable and
Yeah, it's pretty funny. I'm glad he brought it up. Jackie was a fucking worm. Yeah, I remember that
I remember Jackie. What happened to me got kicked off the show
Yeah, he asked for more money. That's what it was. He asked for more money. Yeah. Yeah, because I mean he was
They would let him promote his stupid joke machine. Yes stupid. Like he's like his special. He's like
He's like he had the 900 joke line or something. I don't know
Then this was all before the big deal with serious radio. Yeah, and he would have made all that money anyway if he stayed
Yeah, and then he felt like a big fucking idiot for leave
Guys, yeah, here's the link again. I'm so sorry here. That's what he brought arty and instead lose way funnier than Jackie
It says join stream yard. So it's not work. The leak is not working right now. Maybe it's not working
Okay, we're first with some some people doesn't work. It's weird. It happened to me a bunch of times Wow
Yeah, I don't know what you have to do to change it. It's some
Yeah, sometimes the website goes down. Oh, here's Jamie risk
Oh, hi everyone. What are y'all doing? Jamie? What up?
What up?
Just hanging out and you know, I cleaned up my house today. It's like feeling really good and
There's my shows a
Been doing pretty good. I'm slow. I look at you. You had spunky up there. God. Yeah. Yeah, you met God of Jamie Rose or Gotti
Oh, let's see here which one which one of these guys would be them is it's a guy above you
I mean he or like, oh, we see here. We're next to you now. I put him right next to you
He's somebody else's picture God say something to Jamie Rose
Hey Jamie, how you doing? I'm doing well. How are you? You sure? I'm very sure you don't sound sure
Why I don't know you said I'm doing very well. How are you?
That's just my voice you fucking say you're the fucking smile next time
What'd you say?
I said say it with a fucking smile.
You sound like you got a little shit-eating grin.
I do. I do have one.
Shit-eating grin. That's all you do.
It's fucking people up here with a shit-eating grin.
Yeah, that's me.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Why do you do that?
Don't ask stupid questions. It's your thing. Do you mind? Do you mind asking stupid questions?
There's two other people on the panel. That's the most stupid question. I think they'll be okay if we take the spot.
No, no, no, that's all right. I don't answer stupid questions like that. You don't have to. Okay, let me ask you another question.
Where's your girlfriend tonight?
She's right here. Oh, can I talk to her?
Yeah, go ahead. Hello?
Hello, who's got his girlfriend? Sure. Okay. Are you a puppet?
Yes, my name venanza Joanna
Yeah, so psyche please do not
Okay, I'll tell you it can oh shit. Yeah, she is there. She is right here
Hi destiny
Hello, how are you guys good? How are you Jesus? What's with the manly voice? What the fuck?
Calm down, Scotty. Calm down. I'm a woman. Okay. Are you sure?
She's not
There's just a Marie
Oh
Destiny likes vagina, right? Oh my god. Yeah
Don't tell that I like women
She like women she like a woman
Exactly, yeah
I live in a democracy
I can't do whatever I want to
Hi
She can do whatever she wants
I just want to say what's up
That's why everybody's turning gay man
We don't want to talk about gay shit here man
Hey, why the fuck
Why do you carry for people?
I can't see you boys, is that you?
I can't really hear
I can't see you boys
Is that you?
I'm sick of my undies and the lazy boy.
Talking to loud who is that only he would talk about a lazy boy
All you motherfuckers are lucky you're even allowed on this shit without camming up
Fucking you Chris gay nobody wants to came up man. All right
I'm your gay down
What's the girl what's she doing? Who's the psyche? What's the girl man?
Overriding everybody
Jamie Rose we're talking about what girl? Oh
Destiny are you cool? Are you just gonna hang out or are you gonna like just like
Do you agree that the US is slowly oh my god
Dude, she does this on every panel. Hey
We're talking we're like we're like all getting drunk and like that. I'm not in the mood to talk about this
I want to talk about this
There's sugar, but
What am I to talk about that I'm gonna
Why doesn't
What does it matter you drunk again? Are you drunk again?
Hey
What are you saying?
You made lasagna?
Onion?
Yeah, Jamie Rose is punking you and all of us here. I'm serious. I'm serious. Yeah, I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm serious
What was with you fuckers? Oh, sorry. Were you busy Jamie? Sorry to interrupt. No, no worries.
Jeez
I don't like that woman man, let me let me tell you about the let me tell you about the first time
First time I met Jamie Rose we were backstage after it's like he shut down the panel on somebody
We were back there all she did was ask me these questions about like trying to analyze me and get into my brain and stuff
After about six or seven lies, you know, I finally got bored and said I had to go but that was the first time I met Jamie Rose
Yeah, oh, yeah, yeah, you're the guy with like the crooked you can't even like crop that satanic symbol right?
I remember you that's not me dumb dumb. That's him
Who has this is a simple car?
I do not know who has that you have it on your forehead diggy. I knew I heard
You do
Yeah, I know the symbol
What is it you carved it you carved it in you carved it in there
Harbit I got a tattooed on there. Oh, you have a tattoo in your chin of a pentagram. Yeah
Okay, okay
What is it?
I
Was with life and everything
Don't take no for an answer
He doesn't even know this
That's even better
Live stream it
you. Hey, wait a sec. Wait a
sec. She paid for this panel.
You can do that. It's okay.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. By the way,
what is it? There's one more
hour. There's one more hour
remaining of the of the panel.
One more hour. No, no, no. If
he paid for it, no, it's two
hours. No, yeah, it's two hours.
I said there's one more hour.
So, she paid at 830 and so it's
930.
Thank you both for having all of us to be here for.
You're not even in Brazil, you don't have a Brazilian ass and nobody knows what you actually
look like anymore.
Hey Destiny, it's not going to work, Destiny, you're not going to, no one's going to talk
to you, understand you, and I'm sorry.
I know what you look like, Destiny.
Boom!
Out!
Yeah.
Hey wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
You know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you
Well, yeah, I just think I think I'm just trying to like run have the panel code. She was like
You know that you kick ass as well. Thank you. Thank you
He does kicks ass
I will be no, but I mean
You want to keep it going at 10 30 at 10 30 if someone 10 cents in there $10 cash up
I'll keep it open, but I mean, it's like I'll just take a little break. Is it free after midnight
Let me see
It'll be free. It'll be free after oh, I don't know it. I don't think I don't think I think it will be like
I'm free like one day a week. I think I'm like on Sunday
And she comes back in and she's like no no you better watch mouth like what happens then no she can't
Yeah, I was gonna say that yeah, that's horrible. Oh my god, you lost the leg. Why did you lose the leg though?
I don't know, it makes me wonder if he had diabetes or something.
Oh, no, and you know what it was?
He was in a car accident a few years ago,
and it was complications from that.
Poor guy, man.
Yeah, that's terrible, man.
It was a bionic leg.
He could wrestle again.
Yeah.
Who is it?
Buff Bagwell?
Oh, I don't know.
He was in WCW, Ziggy.
Oh, I don't watch wrestling.
What do they call him?
Buff Daddy?
Yeah.
Sounds like it's only I don't meet buff daddy
Is it sounds like it sounds a little bit like a porn a gay porn star's name, but
He used to have his mother oil him down all right before the matches all the time
Well, that's like a lot of it. That's like that's like some Italian stuff. It's like they get the rig close
What was that really big dude that fucking like he had to take a chair out to fucking drive his car and shit
Oh, that was Andre
Yeah, the giant
I don't know. I don't know what he was in he was in he was in that movie the princess bride, right? That's right
Yeah, he should be in porn with fucking destiny, you know, I think he hasn't he died
Oh my God, Ziggy, now you're too annoying.
Okay, go away.
Okay, I mean, you need to write on your, like, a Z.
Okay, get a book on comedy.
Just get any book.
It's like, pretty much any book.
Just read any book on comedy, and then, I don't know.
Right, you can write, then you can write jokes.
I don't know, I think you are getting confused with like,
I don't even know, you just talk a bunch of nonsense.
It boils, sneak into the room and fart in the room while she's sleeping.
She really does it to me, man, when I'm awake.
Yeah, you might as well do it to her.
Dude, did you run to the shower?
If she wakes up, tell her I said it's okay.
Did you run to the shower thing? I was trapped in the shower and she came in there and fucking took a dump, dude.
And I couldn't get out because I was in that fucking shower.
That's right. That's nasty, dude.
It was a nightmare.
If a woman did that to me, I'd break up with her right away.
It was a fucking nightmare.
No, we want to see that I threw up dude. Do I literally threw up dude like when I'm taking a shower
I was like God is nasty. I don't mind if he's taking a dump on taking a shower
But don't don't wake your ass, you know it
What is it guys? Okay guys? I meant to kick all y'all off and just they call the panel off it right now
Okay, wait, we're still got an hour to go. I don't want to hear about the way the topic is disgusting. Okay. I don't care
It's okay, I mean
I don't want to just talk about
I don't know. I hear shit
You see what happens when it's all dudes on the panel?
That's why you need a girl on the panel.
What happened to Jamie?
She fucking ran off.
Hey, I was a little bit too much of a locker room for her.
Jamie, come back and ask us some stupid questions.
No, no, no.
You need somebody else.
Everyone can hang on this panel because now it's getting more serious.
Yo, I haven't you know I haven't come up here no more. I haven't seen him in a long time now
Yeah, we hope you don't give me the covers we didn't like who talked destiny
Oh sweepy destiny has been on for hours and hours and hours. She just goes. I know I'm
from
And it's like for it goes off for hours and we're like hello and like and so let's talk, okay
And then she's like talk about America and stuff and like get off play. I'm like, okay
And she then she's been in summer was like she's like I want summer's like do I eat my pussy?
And did you say that summer? She said the emers like they like and she's like, yeah
Remember there's there's there's there's
I miss that miss that
What what happened with Trump man, he's supposed to put the sugar
No, you didn't hear me
Let's not talk about let's not talk about mr. Mr. President. I was just addressing the mr. President and
Summer come on up so she can get all fucking horny when she hears your voice
Yeah, demiruses just here she was just here for a few minutes remember when destiny was coming on to page. Oh poor page
She felt so uncomfortable
It was worse than it when any other any guy did it to her
She was turning red. Everything was going on man. It was bad
See you guys, it's when I do need a woman. Oh, so we need a woman on the panel now. I guess right. Hello
Hello first off
Hello, I was never I was never talking about this shit. You were talking about
I like to talk about I like to talk about politics and the pagey. I was being nice
I was being nice to her
Unlike you. I was being nice and
What do you mean you were being nice? I never made her uncomfortable. Who she did she got off the panel
What am I trying to tell is that?
Do you recognize that America is in decline right now? This is what I want to talk about.
Why are you letting her up here and then you kicked me?
You're up here now.
Yeah, you're up here right now
You're up here. Why are you asking me if you're if you're why are you asking you why you weren't here because that's in the past now
You're up again. Okay. All right. Yeah, now we have the move on in the future, right? Why is she yeah?
Treats women
Very well better than you. No way
That's why you don't have a girl. I
Doubt you have a beautiful girl friend. Oh, you're very wrong in that factor. Yes. I doubt you
I got a picture right here
I would never show that picture of her yeah, but you never would okay, but please
Don't show me don't show me that person doesn't want to be shot. I know, but maybe they don't want to be shown
She's all she's sure yes, he is he's done that before he's done it before
I was being very nice
Being very nice and polite
What's up everybody?
Destiny also said that she was a
Destiny stand somewhere
Oh yeah
Close to that
What's that?
No I don't know her
Nice to meet you
Thank you
I love this woman.
Woo!
All right. What's her name? Her name is woman. Woman. I am a woman. Where are you from? I'm all women. Oh, me too, baby.
Where are you from, sexy lady?
I'm of him. I'm of him. I'm a lipstick. Uh, you know, that's guy. He put her picture on. Oh
Oh, yeah, no, she's coming later a summer
No, don't don't worry. They never saw me
Summer are you the fucking lip-tar that does BLM match a marches or no? Is that you?
I do marches, but right now we're there at 50 51 marches, so
What for the Brianna Taylor shit or what?
I mean, I do do that, but I'm not gonna talk about that up here
Hey, I don't know why you talk about this like a black-on-white crime is like seven to one for fucking a white victim
So what okay, let's not talk about that stuff
To calm down
Everybody just come down right now. Yeah, who's the fraud behind backstage that's pretending to be me
Um, that is he just it was just it
God eat you honey. Oh, it's just that's Justin. It's just a boy. It's spunky spunky boyfriend. Oh, all right. Yeah
He's gone
Yeah, well he's a dick
Okay, I think I think I made a new song too. I think he's a dick and he's so
guys
We play can we play a song real quick? I here's my name. I have another
Everyone mute for just
Ready, blow!
Hey, hey, hey!
my sweetheart
With your laughs so loud you light up the night
Page with the heart and the jokes that land blonde bombshell with a beer in hand
Yeah, the streets are rough, but we still glide got my panel verse right or dies right by my side when the drama hits
We don't run or flop now. We laugh
It gets crazy, but we never stop together
Panelverse, we're going to the top
Christine, you're the healer
The heart's so wide
You check on the broken, you stand with pride
Crystal, you're chaos, and I say that with love
Sultry, you turn up the flame.
And Eldo, the trucker, may you steer this game.
From highways to hijinks, from Tehran to Teeth.
This ain't just a show, it's community.
Together, panel, verse, we're going to the top
So, light up that screen, bring the drama in truth
We're messy, we're magic, we're uncensored youth
Psyche's not perfect, but I know what I've got
And that's you, my heart, my fam, my ride to the top
Let's ride, panel, verse, to the top we go
What's my care?
Not beautiful. I think that was it
Who wrote that?
Key. Yes. Yes, and I assisted with the promptings
Yes, it has this a little bit of information. I
Like that
I've been have I've actually I have a I'm gonna have like whole albums full of material
I got you guys really oh shit
No, they're gonna get better, too.
So Spunky is really good.
Spunky paper is good.
And you kicked Justin off the screen?
Yeah, yes, because Justin was talking during the song.
Oh, come on up, Justin.
You can come back.
He's not here.
He left.
And then, uh, but he also was.
His policies aren't tonight.
He was being rude to yeah, he's being pretty rude to summer. Didn't you hear about Goddy? Yeah, I'm not gonna talk about Brianna Taylor
Yeah, let's not talk about that stuff. There's no need to talk about that stuff. Yeah, that's what I'm saying
I was my neighbor and I'm not going to do that. Okay
Peter now you still have hair
I don't know, I've never seen Beta.
Yeah, so Destiny's backstage, but it's like,
I mean, she's like, she was being so loud during the song.
How disrespectful could you be of Destiny?
The only thing I can do I can show my boobs
You can only show your cleavage not your boobs. Yeah, you're not
They're probably hairy anyway, no tatas no tatas only in bra
Don't speak Spanish mother fucker. I speak Portuguese
You're done
Oh, you get tattoos already like you.
I like you a lot.
I love the blue and yellow.
You're tattooed up like me.
I fucking like her.
Yeah, I got like a lot of tattoos.
Fuck you.
I would love to.
You this nose on my back, you know, just
Don't get too excited destiny. Don't I don't get too fucking excited
Yes, yes, yes, she's talking about okay, you know, she's lesbian and she's a girlfriend, right? You have a girlfriend destiny
What's her? What's her name?
I have a beautiful girlfriend. I really love her but
What if I say a beautiful girl if I say a beautiful girl, I was just to tell that she's beautiful
She beautiful or is she like why don't you ever came up for us?
Why don't you came up?
You're from the black Lagoon listen
Because there's a lot of people who hate me. They were trying to dox me and my family
What's that he's showing something
Yeah, I'm fucking tatted all the way man
That's just a contest. Yeah, let's say
Ever take off your hat. We'll do the cat on everybody. That's a test you contest
My legs my belly my chest my back my ass my feet everything
Fucking thing
Yeah, yeah, I hate shitty tits
Yeah, it's like, you know, some people I did whatever, but yeah, I like sucky as a good one. I forgot about that one with the horn
I know my I would like to reduce some of my like, you know, at least they or maybe like, you know
Do some might be different me, you know, fill up my arms a little bit, but you know, they are expensive and the ones I have
I prefer basically
What is that traded? What is that?
It's a go-ahead symbol. Oh, who is that I pose is that oh, is it oh my gosh? Yeah. Yeah
Are you so many demons? Yes? Yeah?
He's
Summoning I'm summoning you know, are you I do you identify with that do you identify with I'll
So I like you are you're too, but I don't know do you do you do you summer to like me?
Know but do you identify with that spirit though with their spirit though?
That you feel that you are like I post
I'm not I post. No, I can't be he's already is in person, right?
Okay
I post he is zesty. He right person
So
Now that's where the word zesty came from
Today
There is a misconception about people with a lot of tattoos
Like a mother oh nice pineapple. Oh, it's very nice
You know they say pineapple kills parasites. Oh, you should oh, yeah
You know pineapple is also not made up to Hawaii it was brought in to Hawaii
Oh, I had actually had no pineapples before they brought it in but now it's a dole family brought them in. Yeah, that's true
Yeah, true
You know, I never even knew about pomegranate until I was fucking like 20
What is from what you we read up you read about for Stephanie or how'd you read that's true Linda? I am
What
for Stephanie, the pomegranate,
she eats the pomegranate, sees it, she gets it.
Pomegranate, yeah, I never knew anything
about pomegranate at all.
That's true, that's true Linda.
I'm not.
Beautiful fruit.
Very healthy.
Beautiful fruit. The more you eat,
the more you shoot.
Remember that.
Peaches are good, yeah, I like peaches.
Beans, beans, the magical fruit.
Beautiful.
I don't like that people see 3 and 4, it's 4 Brody things, remember that.
And what are you worried about anybody doxing you in a whole different country show your face?
Yeah, exactly
I don't want to show my face because I know how these people are, you know, I just want to keep
But you get up here and you say things to the women right and some of them get uncomfortable
Some of them like it but you had behind this big d like
It's it's hard
Nothing you're really saying has any tangible substance and so you you know I'm saying show something hard
It's hard you don't get it that a lot of people that they hate to me
I don't give a fuck what you're talking about you live in a different country, so you don't live here in the United States
It's not it's not about you. It's about other people
Right
But so what who cares if people don't like you you live in a different country
You get so far
That on your say
Some people they're crazy, you don't know you don't know that
Just just have a party in my street
I'd be more impressed. It's like, you know, you showed something of yourself. Otherwise, you're just a talk-on-bubble and that doesn't really get anybody's pussy wet
Like I know Paige was a little like, you know what I mean? They said she was a little uncomfortable, which don't ever make my
I don't know Paige. I have to talk to her
Be nice to her. She is. She really is. Yes. Actually, she's from Canada and she really she's
the sweetest lady we got on here. She's the sweetest lady we have on here.
Of course, yes, yes, yes. And I told her, I would never disrespect her, you know. And I have a girlfriend
and I want to shit on her. I just like to...
You're gonna
Destiny I don't hear about you like you like doing scat play or something. I don't want to hear about it, please
Just said that I have
girlfriend, and she really loves me, and I love her.
It sounded like you said you were going to be an honor.
That's exactly what it sounds like.
Of course you are.
That doesn't sound like pure true love.
Maybe it's true love.
I don't know if you like that.
Is that what Brazilians do?
I don't know what it's like.
What I'm trying to say is that when I see a beautiful woman,
I just say that they're beautiful.
Oh, you can't control yourself, huh?
Yeah
You shit on your girlfriend, why would you do that?
That doesn't mean I will shit on her
You said you would
You did! You said that to shit on her!
It sounds like that's what you said.
She said that to shit on her. What did she say?
I like to shit on her?
I never say that. I never say that.
You don't make any sense anymore.
You say things and you say you don't say them.
I hate when people do that. You have to be kicked off.
Just get to start being honest.
You're not really bringing anything to the table except the big letter D.
That's not really impressing anybody.
Especially not me.
That's not the kind of deals like he's interested in.
Don't do that man.
You called me wrong.
Who called me wrong?
Well, if you're going to have a big D,
you need to bring big D energy.
Are you like, are you like 500 pounds, honestly?
Are you like 500 pounds with like a big,
like a bottle of Everclear in front of you
that's about to like, you know, fall off the table?
That's what I'm picturing.
That's what she's telling me, so prove me wrong,
prove me wrong.
Okay, she looks like that she doesn't came up. She looks like that
No, no, no, no, you don't
What am I chocolate her
And we're like, you know, we love talking about you destiny. Do you want to shit on me? Hey, Barbara?
Destiny
Yeah
Yeah, you should like you stress. I don't I don't I don't I don't wonder I'm not doing that unless he paid $800,000 by like an Arabic chic
Okay, you gotta eat McDonald's first. I know I'm gonna be flowing out there
I have to get a little bit more famous on YouTube though before I get
to run
That's the next level of a little bit of luminosity for me. Okay, so don't remind me, please
I like to talk to women more than men because women we understand each other maybe I understand
people I mean I understand people too I'm not a woman but it's like I think you have
But I do see it because some people say yeah, some people say I'm with your I think you with your suit coat on looking all professional
Okay, you're trying to get somebody. Yes, you do
I think I look good, but uh
Thank you. Yeah, and I have like I have like a bunch of them and it's like they actually they they sent them to you like they put you in all
these outfits and then
You know right and then they they have this all the clothing like and like usually it's usually all on sale and stuff like that
And then you can like if you like you'd like to look of it, whatever, you know
From when you modeled and then you know what I mean like so I can
I can you know I mean like I can see that like so
Yeah, I wish I was
Dressing you up a little bit fixing the picture up a little bit. It was still obviously you you know what I mean
So yeah, I mean, it's pretty much just the head. They sometimes he has a hair a little bit
But it's like, you know
I'd like to be married. Are you single are you single weekends?
Yes, I'm very single. Okay. All right. Okay. Are you single summer?
No, I'm married. You're married. How's the
marriage life for you? It's wonderful. I'm married to my best friend. So I mean it's we have a very
We get each other, you know what I mean? So we let we allow each other to be each other. We just I don't know
He's my best friend. Oh
That's great. Yeah
Congratulations
Haven't been married 17 years together 18 years
No, that's great. Yes. Congratulations. Thank you
Does anybody code this can anybody decode this this message on the screen? It says psyche
I have a request and once you master it. I'll donate the cups from pitch perfect thing. I don't know what it's called
If anybody have any idea what that means you need a set of plastic cups. Okay, so you have that like your beer
I don't have you know, I'm not doing two girls one cup
I'm not doing that but I will do like the ping-pong like your pong or something
But I'm not doing two girls. Hey, I don't know and it's okay. I don't even do a nation
There's people are gonna be eating shit in my presence. And so no, thank you
I mean, I don't know that's why two girls one cups is it right?
So that's what's one form bomb you with that movie the other day. Was that you got a form bomb you know, he said no
Wow, but that you got either that a poor mommy with two girls one cup because you said the next day you mentioned that you just
I requested it though. What are you really pulling bomb by it? Yes
When that's funny
Not that that's funny that happened to you
But we were talking about that on my channel the other night because I was trolling J1 because he always asked questions, right?
And so like I was like, you know what they want
I'm gonna ask you a bunch of questions
So I just asked just a bunch of silly questions like about sex and stuff because it makes them
Giggly uncomfortable because he's shy and I told him what I thought I was like
So if you ever heard of two girls that I kept he was like what and so we started telling him what it was
And oh my god, he was like
Okay, I gotta go but that was part of the deal run. He couldn't leave. He had to say it kind of you know
Should have told him what it was. You should have made him go watch. We did
No, I didn't do all that, but we did tell him what it was but very very graphically what it was
It's so good. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah
Find a funny something you'll find it like not but I mean something like yes. Oh, it's completely fucking wrong
After that, it's just funny
Yeah, yeah, you know, it's fake. You know, it's funny. Well, yeah, it's chocolate yogurt and stuff. Okay. Was it yogurt? Oh, no, it was breathing like that. Desi, are you having to orgasm? What's going on?
She is.
I don't know. That was weird.
What are you doing?
I have had sex with her before.
She sounds like you're on a breathing machine.
Why does he do that for but it doesn't mean I can't I can't have an orgasm with a woman
You you
What the fuck
We were
Somebody give you orgasm
You put me back there and I'm kind of ready to go to be okay. I'll go go lay go go that you're ready to go and go
Had sex with them
They wanted to date me every time every time I went out on the street today, they were always calling me
They're always like hitting on me, you know
But I am not attracted to men. This is just my nature. This is how I am
I mean, I'm you know, I'm not actually I like women and men so, you know, everybody has their thing
What was going on Goddy? She's just a more man for psyche. That's all
I don't understand people are just different I had sex with them that that's not a problem
if to talk about that I can talk about that I think women are beautiful I think women
I think
Beautiful I put them on I put them on like a level of like a like you know goddess
We get no I'd like you know right goddess is on the on earth right and then I have and they're also the mothers
And so they are like, you know
Likey, that's why you're gay. You put the pussy on the pedestal man
It's random guy, oh, it's random
How you doing? Hello, man. There's J1. J1. What's up with the two girls on a cup? Tell them how you learned about that the other night
Oh my god
Did you walk you yet? I just ate somewhere
I don't I don't want to hear that about this. I mean I know the plot. I really don't want to hear. Yeah, you got to go watch it though
He was talking about so I had to you know, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry
I was talking about them. I'm not sorry
This is what I want to say may don't know how to lick pussy and the women
I would have to disagree with that, I would have to disagree with that. I don't know. Maybe you just had a guy that didn't know how to do that.
They don't know. I haven't been with a guy before. They don't know how to proceed with it.
I've been with a guy before. Well, man, that works very well.
I can tell you that you've been definitely, well, not all men maybe, right, but maybe you just got a fluke, but like my husband, I mean, he's great pussy.
like and I you know I'm not you know I wasn't a virgin so like yeah I'm sorry you didn't have
that good experience you know what if you saw what she looks like you'd understand you understand
why she feels that bad right someone she's a big greasy slob
Now she could have just got me don't get me wrong. There's guys out there. Don't know what the fuck they're doing
So, you know, I mean, so maybe she just got one of those
summer
Yes, I have a legitimate question for you. So you said you've been happily married for like eight seventeen years, right?
Yeah, and you talk about all this bisexual activity. So my question to you is
Do you and your like husband joy?
Is there like three ways going on?
Yes, there are. I'm sorry. I didn't mean to say.
I mean, me and my husband are very happy in what we do and what we do is
Have fun. So that was yes. That's all that matters. He's always a part of anything I ever did
That's pretty cool
That's like a lot of guys dreams though. He's very lucky, but it's like isn't it kind of like awkward sometimes because it's like
You know if you like if you bring out somebody that he was like to agree with it
You're like, would you be like it? Oh
You're thinking about your experiences
You know, I mean like it's this is different like we don't get jealous ever summer
What if he gets a little excited over the other now?
No, no human human nature. I'm saying I'm saying human nature is like
Women I think are by nature a little bit more jealous. The men are very jealous. You can't speak that first of all
You're not a woman
And you really don't handle women on that level
So and I'm gonna tell you as far as me goes you can't speak for me because you the women you know
Maybe like that. I'm not speaking for you. I'm not speaking for you. I'm just saying class
People that are in that lifestyle
just think differently. So it's a little different than, you know what I mean?
I'm sorry to make you a suit. I didn't mean to.
She's a sister-wife. Summer's kind of like a sister-wife.
I am. I'm not a sister-wife.
Sounds like it.
No.
I don't know
No, she's a she's she's like swings swings or something like that swings
Just because you have fun every great now and then does it mean you have sister wife's or your swingers or any of that?
Just because you have fun every now and then does your husband let you
Bring talk about because that part of you know what I mean?
I was one of those your husband let you bring dudes into the mix or what?
I don't I don't want to so I don't have the need to do that. That's the right answer
What?
Oh, oh, yeah, that's not my thing. Yeah, I mean that's good for him. I guess
That's the way to be
Every single way possible mentally
You're a good girl summer
Happy wife happy life, right
He's a provider and a protector and he does every you know what I mean like he's everything. I love my husband
The wife's happy no one's happy
He's the only person that can leave me because otherwise I'm just crazy
But when it comes to him, I'm submissive. That's my husband. I love him
That's good. That's good. But have you ever been with a woman summer?
Before yes
I think ever girl has you know, they're just curious
My sex life is absolutely terrible. It's terrible. It's just been like if you heard of the Mojave desert, it's even worse.
Well, when you were having sex, were you a swinger?
Or was I whatever no, no, I was like really from it
I was like really wanting to have sex like like really pretty like you know when I was like a teenager
And we just came up with a well and stuff like that and I was to go in the chat rooms and you know
I met somebody it was like a pipe, you know
So that was like my first experience.
I was basically, that was my wild times for my teenage years.
My teenage years of my 20s, and I didn't even have that many wild times.
I was like always just like so insecure and shy.
I could hardly talk to people.
And so I never really talked about my waste of my time.
But not everything's about sex.
It's about love.
What about you random guy?
What about me?
Do you ever I don't know what your sex life like I'm just boring. I got a regular girlfriend. We do our thing
It's normal. Nothing crazy. No
Three girls
How's your sex life? It's great got three girls
Oh, yeah
Isn't that very expensive to have three isn't like one very expensive like how it's really expensive psychosis. It's hard man. It's really hard
Well, how many jobs do you work? Are you like a millionaire? I mean it's like
Are they locked in a cage in your house or are they like for people to roam free
But this bullshit talking about I have to be with the critter
So if you love someone it's enough only one person is enough
Not after me
I need six
I know my god, that's too many
Joking I'm joking. What do you just like over and pop it in like it's like moved on the line
Then you go over like that's cool. Yeah, smack that
What about you God? Oh, I'm inside every woman that embraces me
And no real a girl that you you will love for the rest of your life
You don't need to have two three girlfriends. You just
You just need to love to one one woman in your life
Do you have one you love? Do you have one you love?
Of course I have. I just told to have a girlfriend and I really love her.
You just said you're going with it like three weeks ago.
Oh my god. No, I don't like that shit.
Oh
We don't need that we don't need that I've never
to kiss and make love and love each other. This is not about only sex, just about feelings.
Yeah, but that's what we're talking about at the moment. Like, it wasn't going to just
be about my sex life. Y'all didn't think that, right? No, we're going to have a whole conversation
because we're all adults, so I wasn't asking you. Everyone else answered, so we're asking
Some women they don't like intercourse just like myself. I haven't been with the men
I had sex with them. I had the within course, but I don't like intercourse
So my girlfriend
And that's cool, I mean, you know, whatever
Everyone shared a thing they liked and or what they did or didn't do so that's we just now it was your turn. That's all
You're doing okay, Destiny. You're doing better than me. I'm scared of women. I've never witnessed a woman.
I was kind of dexterous. So, hey, Excel. How you doing, babe? How's your sex life these days?
Do you ever kiss a woman?
Never, no.
Oh my god. Never give a kiss to a woman?
He's got that hot wife. What are you talking about?
What did he say? Why do you always lie to me, babe? I feel like he's pushing me away.
Have you seen his wife?
She's a black black lady. I got her on the phone. She's a smoke show. Yeah, she's beautiful
I don't understand why people think we
Is the echo in the room
Are you in the bathroom?
What are you doing?
Get off the toilet. Please don't be on the toilet on my show.
Even God answered her question about sex so it's like chill out.
Is that a voice change?
Destiny has a voice changer, huh?
I got her out of here.
She needs a face changer.
You've been sitting up there.
Oh, go ahead Excel finish tell us about your sex life. You know me and my wife get down
I mean I got the option. I already you know
But you women are crazy, I can only go one of y'all
Yeah, I love your wife though. She's amazing and she's hot so like you got a you got a good one. She's beautiful
She is a queen. Hey Zyle, didn't you guys say you have a swing in the bedroom?
Yeah, sir. Yes, sir. See you just swinging her back and forth. Yeah, we have all kinds of fun things. So, yeah
I'm so in a dieting nest necessary. You see how smart teacher is already
You know, you're gonna be with somebody right you're gonna be with just that person you know, I'm Sam
You have I don't know make it interesting to have fun. That's what it's supposed to be, right? They always, you know
Hold on one second
You just sit up here
What's this you're gonna be a porn bomb
Sushi homemade sushi. Oh, no, that's Jim cat. Okay. Never mind. She's not gonna form home. That looks bro. It looks like a baby chick
It's sushi
Yeah, it's all made to see the room. Yeah. Yeah, but you got a bunch of stuff on top of it
Yeah, that's gross. I did what I do. I'm sorry. I want to have a sidebar
Yeah, sidebar question summer. So you've been married 17 years. How often do you think like how many times a week?
do you think it's a normal healthy section it's each person's different you know i mean yeah
i don't know what i'm going for you and hey day man you're so very healthy yeah i mean multiple
times a week at least okay once a month i think he means uh he means with himself though
someone he means with himself i mean well that you know you and yourself can have that conversation
Once a month do one come on
You're knocking them all off at once
So I have this greatest trilogy book it's called
It's called bored on a rotten day
But it goes over all the signs in the dark side of the sign and I've been reading about it's different signs
But I was wondering it does have it like little sections it has like small sections
And so if you want me if you want to tell me your spouses
Sign that I can tell you what your space the jedger for your spouse of the sign of your date
So it'll tell you the bad quality. I don't know that I can't know funny way
Not like in a mean way, but if anyone's interested in like quick shit, so if you throw out a sign and I can read something
about the sign
Go ahead
All right, no way I'm dealing with me and my wife are both fire signs. You're both fire. So what's what's your wife's that?
What's your wife's sign?
A Leo and I'm an Aries brah. Okay, so she's a Leo. Okay, so I'm gonna read about the Leo woman
If you're like, you know, if you're in love with a Leo, okay, or if you're with a Leo, okay, a Leo woman
And it will say, okay, it says if okay. Oh shit
Yeah, I want you to read my next. Okay for sure
Okay
Sorry
J1 oh here I am
You got one of the ladies take care. I'm not right. I'm in his three ladies
I love him though, he's a good kid
Well, he's like a big guy or whatever
Oh my gosh, mate
It's kind of like it's going slow. I'm so sorry guys just right there
Do you got something where you bear the signs to each other?
Because that's where you get down to the real hot fire you messed that our couple is
Well, you know, okay, so so I know I'll tell you just what I know about like a Leo
First of all because I dated Leo doubt that the one woman I dated was the Leo and so and I have my brother's Leo and
Okay, so they're born. I think that probably the hottest time of the year, right? They can like in July probably and
they
There's a fire sign of the sun
So they're very egotistical and they want things everything revolves around them everything's about you know
It's so they insist on like having all the attention on them
Um, usually they went and then they're very, um, explosive, they can be very angry. They do remind you of like she did remind me of like the sun.
Like she's very like sun, like, you know, just like the astrological quality of the sun of like, you know, just including like she was a very large ball of gas.
But, but anyway, but oh yeah. So, oh, I think I got it. I think I got it. Okay. So you said Leo, I'll tell you about Leo. Okay.
OK, so Leo, if you love one, if you love one, Leo, woman.
It says, just put on your resume that you've worked for Martha Stewart.
That's more valuable than all the overtime I could pay you, Martha Stewart.
She's loyal, steadfast, and her animal magnetism is tangible whether she's wearing blue jeans
or a business suit.
The Leo woman seeks a mate who is attentive, romantic, and hardworking.
She's sentimental, fun-loving, and her view of life is refreshingly simple.
All ways here are the Queen's ways.
This line from Alice's Adventures in Wonderland describes with near perfection,
Leo woman's personality. Remember this, and chances are you too will get along fine.
If you refuse to acknowledge her omnipresence, remember this warning.
No matter how quiet or charming your lioness appears on the surface,
her metaphorical claws are just as sharp as her four-legged sister roaming on the plains of Africa.
She's more hussy than heinous. This woman carves just as many notches in her
headboard as her male counterpart does and is the one woman in the
universe who writes her own phone number in the locker room wall. She loves the
mirror as much as Lieber does and lives in luxury as does Capricorn. The
difference is her mirrors are guilt edged in her line-herbedroom walls
whereas the lady goat will dress expensively but underst...
Aiden, the lioness prefers an Ares Bob Mackie knockoff.
She got on sale.
Her motto is, if you got it, flaunt it, if you don't, fake it.
This is also true in the bedroom.
She may play the sex kitten, but a leo woman is more interested in power than porno.
If you're good looking, have money to burn or a power player or can introduce her to
someone who is, she'll drape herself over your bed or the back seat of your Lincoln.
Just long enough to test whether you know the difference between a radiant cut and princess
If you jokingly say your hairstyle, expect a look that can melt and sand into glass.
If you're serious, you could probably be an Aquarius.
In love, she expects weekly flowers, daily phone calls, a romantic getaway at least once
a month.
Unless you're rich, you better start applying for the low-interest second mortgage.
If you don't want to lose her to capricorn and Gucci loafers, it'll probably work, but
it will spend.
her salary and baseballs makeovers and the latest fad diet. The female lion appreciates humor
hers. She laughs at her own jokes when at full throttle. It can be as loud as Lucille Ball,
Leo Lucille Ball, except you won't be able to turn down her sound and she won't shut up until
she's ready. Those blasé wisecracks she dispenses at dinner seem natural and off the cuff.
Actually, she spent three hours in the internet sorting spams afternoon.
Because Leo May West is a classic example of the archetypal female lion.
West outrageous style and non-stop sexual innuendo were her trademarks only a Leo would have the brass to write produce and star and play
In a play called sex in 1925 she became notorious for one liner such as I'm a girl who's lost your reputation and never missed it and
When I'm good. I'm very good and when I'm bad. I'm better
She was smart sly and way ahead of her time true to her over-the-top Leonine character West pushed her luck long enough
Too long and too hard. At 85, she still wore her hair cascading over her shoulders,
although it looked more like a damp mop than a silky mane. Her makeup was garish and she
propped herself up in the arms of sweating bodybuilders. Young enough to be her grandchildren.
Wes became a caricature. The hooker with a heart of gold turned into a hag who refused to relinquish
the spotlight. Yours won't be quite as vain, but it will demand lots of attention. Whether she's
quiet and regal or slinky and untamed, a Leo woman is high maintenance as they come.
That's it. What is that one? What was that? What was what that was a Leo?
That was the kind of astrological description of a Leo. A Leo woman. Oh
It was a terrible run-off sentence. We could have done without all that. I'm sorry. That was a lot. Yeah
That was
That is that such serious and capital court. I'm a capital court. He's such okay
Okay, so would you like he says there's would you like to hear about him or both of y'all do both?
Okay, okay, so I'll do
Okay
Yeah, I can do both of the sexes. I mean sometimes they're longer than us somewhere longer than that. I think that
But I think they're pretty good. So Sagittarius. Okay
And so he is a Sagittarius so the male Sagittarius
So it is it if you love when a Sagittarius man
Says my divorce came as a complete surprise to me that will happen when you haven't been home in 18 years
Lee Trevino number first
Says he's honest trusting and eternally optimistic
He won't restrict your freedom or expected to drop your nights out with friends in favor of staying home with him
He may have a very protected arrive protective
A perspective on life similar to Mark Twain or the diplomacy of Winston Churchill, an archer
once a companion to accompany him on frequent, spontaneous outings to wonderfully diverse
places because to him, life is to be explored and enjoyed.
Before you decide he's your soulmate, understand that male sedentary is
has the same attitude toward commitment as does his mythological symbol, the centaur.
He spends all his youth and most of his adulthood at a continual heat.
He is an accomplished lover, but it's the deed he desires, not you.
You no doubt fell for his Boy Scout smile and talent for quoting Shakespeare while simultaneously
unfastening your bra.
But as a partner, he makes a great friend when you won't see very often because his
to drop in when he needs to change of clothes or a shower.
Since an archer could happily live in a cape for months,
eating crickets and contemplating his navel,
even if you marry him, you'll feel like you're still single.
Don't expect to lean on his shoulder or cling to his arm.
Do expect to be his pal or groupie
and to spend many nights alone.
He's neither jealous nor possessive.
In fact, he wants you to have a life
Independent of his sense that allows him more time for drinking beer with his buddies and
following with his favorite football team around the nation.
He is the one guy in the universe who is born to be a bachelor.
He won't care how you dress, who your friends are, or where you spend your time as long
as you don't bother him with all the details.
He's too busy elucidating his latest theory for solving all the problems of the world.
Archers have opinions on every subject under their sun and cannot answer even simple questions
Ask if you want a ham sandwich to answer with the history of Earl of sandwich, the 16 different kinds of bread you could use to enhance the flavor of the meat, and the dissertation on mustard.
Michael de Nostradamus, the 16th century French physician and mystic, had the distinct Sagittarian penchant for expounding on the mysterious mysteries of the universe.
In typical archer style, the good doctor's visions were not only voluminous,
totally more than 1,000, but were carefully crafted, allowing
endless interpretations.
This ensured that whatever happened,
he could be credited with prophesizing the event.
Only an archer would be as audacious and irresponsible
as the predicted events 2,000 years in the future.
And only an archer could do it with such a flair
for the art of bullshit.
A male Sagittarius respects authority as long as he's the authority figure.
Question is right to rule and you'll soon understand the meaning of Jupiter's wrath.
He has a nasty temper and his volcanic eruptions result in expensive trips to the nearest home improvement center for wall board, nails and plaster.
He's impulsive, set him up for milk, and he'll come home with reservations for the
midnight flight to Peru.
He might invite you along, and then again, he might tell you that since you both know
he has more fun alone, he bought only one ticket.
If he does take you, you'll spend half of your time dragging him out of the local hot
spots where he's trading pickup lines with the natives, and all the other half tracking
him through the jungle as he searches for the meaning of life.
This is the archers favorite game is bad to worse. Tell him the sink is backed up
He'll flood the basement because he forgot to turn off the water before he tore out the plumbing
Ask him to forego one of the several nights out with his boys in favor of a quiet dinner at home
He'll rant and rave that you're smothering his need of freedom
Even lovable archer Walt Disney had a dark side. Remember all those endearing fairy tales he brought on the screen
Bambi's dead mother and a raging forest fire, the orphan lion king stalked by his own family members,
Snow White and Cinderella, one with a stepmother who wanted to cut her heart out together who was
forced to become a servant in her own home. Yours will step on your toes, bore you with rhetoric
and hurt your feelings with a thoughtless remark, but after all he's a fire-breathing dragon,
but this guy's more like Pete's dragon, Disney's character who flops along, meaning no harm and
leaving little lasting damage.
Well, I will say this as far as like the freedom and stuff all like that
Yeah, my husband totally like that now. He doesn't go out all he does is work and he comes home
That's it. I mean, he's older too. Also, so maybe that has something to do with and he was a flight when he was single for sure
Oh, yeah, he was definitely a flight when he was single, but you know
Yeah, that was funny
Yeah
At all
Yeah, well then that's like, you know, I think like electronics kind of our like the fire element to
But I like that they kind of like talk about like the archer and that's like, you know
That's what the sedentary is is a centaur, but as an art
He's an archer and so that's what they're always like looking like I always think of them as very visionary and they have
Yeah, fire fire arrows of fire. So capricorn woman. So I'm a capricorn man. And so you're capricorn woman
Okay, so I want to read this one and then we'll see if anyone else wants and I'll keep I'll keep the panel open. Okay, so
If you love one a Capricorn woman, okay, so Capricorn woman
It says
It's a good thing. I was born a woman or I'd have been a drag queen Dolly Parton January 19
Every Capricorn woman has a built-in sense of style and social grace
Whether her personality is as a outgoing as Dolly Parton or as coolly reserved as Ava Gardner
Her basic character is practical and sensible. She seeks a mate who is strong and ambitious
and who plans for the future. Since she appreciates the best things in life,
plan to take her to the finest restaurant. Oh, be sure to bring along your stock portfolio
and a copy of your family tree because if one or the other doesn't push her
Leo may be a queen, but Lady Capricorn is pure diva. She can be as emotional as cancer at a pity
party or as pushy as an Aries on a power trip. She's so status-conscious that she won't plan a
vacation until she's checked with her travel agent to see where this year's in spot is located.
She'll pay $100 for a hairdo. She hates if it's the latest style from a hottest salon in town.
In public, she'll be the model of social demeanor because she always has a lookout for someone rich
At home, you'll eat in the kitchen and watch TV in the bedroom because she's afraid you'll get
a spot on the tablecloth or wrinkle the fabric on the sofa. She spends a good part of the day
walking through the house, blowing kisses to all the inanimate objects she so dearly loves.
She's pretentious. She may have been raised under a bridge on the wrong side of the train tracks,
but before she can sense to meet your friends, she'll expect a rundown of their social standing.
Look down on the one who's content to own one service station instead of the gas company
and fawn over the one who just got paroled from jail for creative accounting.
The former she views as lazy, the latter is inspired.
Capricorn hookers are just as snooty mayflower madams
Sydney bitty barrows and Hollywood madham Heidi Fleiss who was who each repeat respectively
Cornered the market on high-class brothels were just as selective about about their clientele and just as socially aware of the public
When asked to comment about being busted bitty told the reporter never say anything on the phone that you wouldn't want your mother to hear at your trial
When Fleiss was paroled
She headed straight for the plastic surgeon
I had a lot done," she said, lips, eyes, ears, boobs, being in prison with no skin care really
doesn't number on you. Yours probably won't be blindly ambitious, but she will have a definite
tendency to embellish the truth with her tea time conversation with friends,
turns to family stories. Her Aunt Mabel, who's the hog calling champion of West Virginia,
might evolve into a much revered acapella singing star of the South.
The Lady Goat is just as humor-challenged as her male counterpart and will mope for days over any off-handed seizing.
Her joke switch is set on dim, and the only time she really smiles is when she's emptying the cookie jar bank to buy another savings bond.
Romantically, she may swing both ways, but she's not into swinging from the chandelier.
However, don't confuse Sirius with Sexless.
Capricorn megastar Marlene Dietrich was known as the love pirate for the shocking ease at which she
stole spouses and lovers away from their partners. She expects to be pursued, wooed, and put on a
mood, and which may give it tiresome after five or six years. Tossing and diving between the sheets
is a surefire way to get her to dive into bed. Or if you aren't rich, make a granola bar.
Capricorn women love little gifts and are always on a diet. Whether yours is the life of the party
Keeping up appearances and long-term security mean more to a Capricorn woman than either a warm blanket or your warm body
That's not like summer. Yeah
Oh, I thought that was for you summer that was for summer that's
My capricorn and an Aquarius
Aquarius you cuz I don't even know Aquarius and Aquarius are quite interesting there are airside and you know
The airside skin like they have swords right there like the airs are swords so they can be sharp, right?
But I will read I'm actually a Aquarius moon. So summer night both capricorn Aquarius kind of mixes
interesting
Um, because I think they are kind of different in the sexes too. Um, so let's see. Where is female, right? Okay. Where is female?
So, yeah, I know
You first females, okay
I know that it was just Gotti playing a prank
I think uh, I think I hope he's okay guys. I guess someone maybe
If you have a guy's phone number make sure he didn't like a ball that ball don't serve
Because if you love it you love one an Aquarius woman if you have your titular room you have your titular recognition
I'll take money and power so actually capricorn and Aquarius are very different signs
And so it's interesting to have the other because they're both next yeah, that's right to both
Yeah, and so but it's interesting that both, you know, I trade supposed to yeah, but more I'm more like emotionally
The aquarium like which I have these cold emotions, but then it's like I'm like otherwise my I'm the earth sign
I said, but anyway Aquarius says she says
You can have your titular record recognition. I'll take money and power and that's Helen girly brown
February 18th, so she's a free spirit. He's eternally curious and always friendly
An Aquarian woman will enchant you with her igniting magic charm and seeks a man who's
both romantic and intellectual.
She is neither possessive nor jealous and believes that love begins with friendship.
She is also a total individual who marches to her own drummer.
Whether this is the beat of a jazz band or a set of town tom-toms as she stakes you
out on the nearest ant hill is something you should try to determine before the wedding.
The good news is that she is one of the nicest people in the universe.
That's because she always does exactly what she pleases, and acquires females rebellious, headstrong, and contrary, she can be selfishly independent and exasperating, especially when she's running through the house, screaming, freedom!
When angry, she can act out in an aggressive, childish way.
She may stamp her feet, order you out of the house,
or even trash the place in a fit of petulant evanation.
But until she approaches anger from the same detached,
mental perspective as she does everything else in life,
preferring to argue and provoke you into a rage,
as all air sign she's easily bored and delights
in stirring the pot, especially if she thinks
it will piss you off.
She's so unpredictable that each time you kiss her or goodbye,
you never know who or what.
will greet you when you return. She has a few inhibitions. Some female worn
barter bears have green hair, purple hair, or no hair at all. She will wear a nose ring,
a toe ring, or six earrings in one ear and a tongue stud. She will dress any way she fancies
no matter what the occasion and is apt to wear a Levi's in a free Tibet t-shirt for a formal dinner
where she will not hesitate to discuss any topic under the sun including death politics,
cannibalism, or cannibalizing dead politicians.
Her personality is combination shock treatment and rugged individualism.
The female water bear loves gossip as much as cousin Gemini.
However, her odd curiosity lends herself into ferreting out the only the most
disgusting bits of information she can find to horrify you with as she unleashes
her maniacal laughter.
She will keep you up all night analyzing such inane topics as how dust bunnies
are formed and whether or not cancer Alex Trebek is really an android.
She has a horde of friends of all ages, sexes, persuasions, and character types, and she
will be available any time of day or night for guiding, counseling, a free meal, or a
warm bed.
If you want to win her heart, be prepared to feel as if you are living in a combination
bus station and therapist's office.
The more bizarre you are, the better your chances of getting her in the sack.
Taylor, you're doing research on vampire sexual rights in Los Angeles, and she'll confess
that she channels new positions for the Kamasutra from Bella Legosi.
Pretend you're an alien sex being from the planet Halcyon, and she'll wrap herself in
Christmas lights and fall at your feet.
However, unless you are in Aries with an endless imagination, or a Scorpio who can appeal to
her perverse side, you'll soon find yourself with a board partner who prefers reading about
to doing the deed. But don't confuse bored with non-sexy. Hollywood bombshell Aquarius
Mamie Van Doran or Mamie Van Doran roared the bullet bra when the Leo Madonna was wearing
diapers and Mamie rarely have ever confused a good lay with a romantic attachment. True
to the clever Aquarian nature, she survived the blonde bimbo era of Hollywood in the 60s
and is still going strong. She still loves men and as she's fond of saying, Mamie likes
Aquarius is not into blatant emotionalism. So if you are a worshiping you need like video or a drama wrench water sign
You'll soon feel like you stumbled through it
Electrally charged whirlwind and then zap snapped and spit out as too stupid to deal with all in record time
Ms. Aquarius has a touch of money grabber in her soul, although she's not as quite as
obvious as Capricorn checking out your Dunnan brand sheet rating.
She does firmly believe in the old cliché and says it's easy to love a rich person
as a poor one.
Charming, stunning, and nine-time married, George Legobore, said once, I've never hated
a man enough to give him back his diamonds.
Gabor's guest role on the last show of the old Batman TV series was typical of the Aquarius female.
Maybe that's why she remembers it so fondly.
Jaja played Minerva, an evil woman who owned a spa for men where she scanned their brains
under special hairdryers.
I loved the character Gabor said.
The wardrobe was all gaudy and silver and nothing could be more exciting than that.
These hairdryers got all the spy stories out of the people's brains.
One person was a jewelry salesman and I could find out the combination to a safe.
I opened the safe and diamonds kept on falling all over me.
I loved it. The title of her autobiography,
one lifetime is not enough sums up the philosophy of every aquarium woman,
including yours. So that's it. Yeah, I like that one.
I've been on a lot of panels and that is a panel killer.
I'm sorry. What was it? You don't listen as your show. I already already got to give suggestions. I'm the suggestion box, dude
Okay, well, you know, I was I gotta do something here
So I'm gonna end this I'm gonna end this panel at 11
It's like somebody would like to donate another $10 and then I'll keep it running. Oh Chris
Three hours after that. Yeah, I'm not drifting
Yeah, I'm now I'm gonna be charging for just starts charging for a more time
Yeah, because the channels are getting very draining and there's like someone sometimes they're like a little bit disrespectful
And it's like and I'm willing to they have that and they have like longer panels if they're entertaining and stuff like that
But I'd say and not willing to be just to be disrespected, but I feel like you wrote those fucking long ass
Things is oh, I know that wasn't about that. I wasn't about that but I'm saying like in general
It's good. Yeah, that's how it's been. So so I did have like last night ghost
Sponsored and then spunky sponsored this this this time of the thing
And so, you know, it just will also keep it more scheduled so I can like, you know
And then it's like I can like you know, and if somebody would like to people can also come together
It's only $10 for the I'm sorry Barbara are enjoyed it. Sorry Barbara. I can't speak for everybody
But I would like to do if anybody wants a reading I would do personal readings
And I leave me be more personal than that than that one was that yeah, that was just fun reading
That was kind of interesting. Yeah, if you were like, I don't know if you're interested in that kind of stuff
Do you like that summer? I really like that was very interesting
And some of you are on a tarot tarot type of channel
So like, you know every now and then he's gonna have his moments where he does his readings and he reads and then we
We act crazy and then he's gonna do his thing and then we get crazy
Yeah, it's like, you know, and you really like, you know, Tarzan kind of crazy, but you know, hey everybody has their thing
I guess I get what you're saying
Yeah, I mean, but yeah, I'm really I'm really trying to put more emphasis on the
Undoing the tarot on the show and also I want to pull like you know cards
I'll just want to put it more through this show. I want the cats are of course all around here
I the cats are a big part of the show again. I wouldn't have the panels and stuff, but you know, it's like
You know, it's like I figure people can love me or hate me, but it's like if they hate me
I could still I have to find a way to monetize or else it's not worth it to do the show
You send 10 bucks summer. I like I kind of I'm running low on cash
Could you send him 10 bucks so we could stay a little longer
No, somebody has somebody I think somebody has somebody will like somebody in the chat
But probably because guys I also I will advertise your like your what time or your website
So we have 15 minutes 15 minutes, I stayed over half I stayed half hour over
But it's how long are you if I said you 10 bucks? How long are you gonna stay on?
nine or three hours
Wow
And that's and I'll open the panel for everybody, you know, and so and I'll also put your name on the banner
See how spunky his name is in the banner and so I'll say thank you
So I don't put your that you're like link to your show on the banner and stuff
Yeah, I'll send it to the book
Thank you so much
Think I would just I'm gonna I won't be here because I could get up early in the morning
But I'll be listening so don't give me some no wait you west coast or you you must be west coast then
Yeah, I'm in Kentucky. It's 146 here Kentucky
Yeah, that's right Kentucky
Y'all
Yeah, I think
Do you have a big day tomorrow? Oh, it's a Saturday. Yeah, we're having a rally. Mm-hmm
Rally what kind of rally is it? Oh, kind of rally
Just
Just want to mention
I know he's the president clearly
Trump rally
No, I don't go to jump rallies, you know
No
That's fine. I went to the one where he got shot. I wasn't there. I went to the second one in the same spot in Butler
Wow down
Yeah
But my family was at the one where he actually got shot
Yeah, and they all like hit the deck
I'm glad your family didn't get hurt
Yeah, but that one Cori guy got shot
Yeah, I was sad. Yeah much. I'm really good. It's just yeah
So I'm looking at is I just found this really cool new app it says it's like weird news
It says psychic and investigators search for missing cat captivates Bolivia. And so the cat
There's the cat right there. All right
And it says, Tito, a gray and white male tabby cat who went missing on a domestic flight last month, looks while being photographed at Taurilla, Bolivia in this undated picture obtained by Reuters.
It says, Mexico City, firefighters, aviation authorities, and most recently an animal psychic.
have joined the Bolivian government's mission to help find Tito, a gray and white male
tabby cat who went missing on a domestic flight last month. The plight of Tito and his determined
owner, Andrea Iture, has captivated the nation. Consumer Rights Minister Jorge Silva said last
week that authorities have even called a psychic to try to make contact and locate the cat.
Through her techniques, the psychic can communicate with Tito to find out where he is.
Silva said in a radio interview,
we are exhausting all our resources to find Tito.
The cat went missing on December 8th.
It tore a recounted on social media posts
that it went viral after she was told by an airline
the cat had to travel in the hold of a plane
flying from Taria to Santa Cruz
when she landed her pets were nowhere to be found.
On December 12, Public Works Minister Edgar Montano announced a big state-led effort.
The cat likes tuna, so we have left out tuna," he told the news conference, adding he suspected
the cat may have been roaming the original airport since the departure date.
Some animal lovers have criticized the airline, BOA, over the missing cat.
BOA as it's said a little publicly there was a recent video for people to stay alert for signs of the cat adding
I have not stopped and I will not stop searching for him. Oh, that's beautiful
Well, they have a second out looking for this cat guys Tito the cat
We found guys this is Bolivia. Yeah, that's a top news in Bolivia one cat
I mean this is like isn't this a little bit
I mean I look at them for the cat is a nice cat
But this is a waste of police resources to me. I mean in Bolivia a lot together. It's a lot
Yeah, it's like, you know, I mean it's like getting it hiring animal psychic. I mean that that's every now you're getting
Bolivia, I mean come on
Probably rich and don't have this sounds like it sounds like a money. It's like a money laundering scheme to me
Oh, yeah, what is it if animals taking some Bolivia? That's it
Right, I should become an animal psychic though. I mean I can talk to animals, too
Especially cats one of the ladies that it goes out with us on Wednesday night
That's she always says summers are animal whisperer because I always take care of the animals like I always have food and leashes and all that shit
I like animal
Yeah, I love animals too
Yeah, you remind me a lot of my mom like my she just like
Well, my mom has a heart for every animal. She raised birds and like little parrots and like
Yeah, I won't bring him home, but I do
Got only my two babies at home lesson. This is my only pussy. He says no more
This is no more. Some of my cats are like that. They can only have two kitties. That's enough for me. I'm too busy for all this
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. So I'm sorry random guy
I was I mean I found this app and I thought it would be interesting
I mean it's kind of a boring story turns out like that and I alright random guy
Well, I've got to send him $10. So turn the fuck up. I'll see you guys a little bit. I love you summer
Thank you. Are you there?
Oh, yeah, he jumped off. Well, I'm gonna put
Yeah, well, I'll be here. I'll be right here if they can't the part of the panel will be open
And I'm sure people know about and if I can't sleep, I'll come back
I'll send it to you in a second. Let me follow there. I love you so much. Good night. All right. Y'all have fun tonight
Thank you
How are we guys doing? Yeah, and so yeah, I think that's also like cool that
Like I'm gonna put, you know, I'm thinking like for people that do sponsor it
I will put hey random guy. Did you try to come back up? I will put their
If they have YouTube page, I'll put the YouTube page or their business or favorite website or whatever on the banner
And so that's advertising and so that's a good and if multiple people come together
You can put a couple of advertisements on it. And so
Just a way for like, you know
Make sure no matter what you know
that
Show is gonna stick around because I really wanted to I really like love to do it
But I do not want it to be a hobby. I want this to be like my full time. You know, you're in a broke. Oh
It's cool it does that sometimes
Wow, it says Trump's who's Wall Street Journal or EPS CIN report six ten billion. Oh my god
Trump is that crazy and say what if this person's not even real and now there's there's 10 billion law or lawsuits over them
You know, isn't that crazy?
Seems like a little bit insane to me
Okay
So let me see, do I have anything to read to you? I can read you a spiritual book, or maybe a short chapter of something.
But these are very, these are kind of advanced though. I mean, it's like, okay, I'll start reading this book to you.
This book is called The Comp de... Oh, oh.
One moment, hold on, hold on, hold on. Oh, shit.
Hello
Okay, this is my real name Jennifer Martins. Ah, I don't have anything yes, and
This is my girlfriend
You see all the picture
If you want to search, if you, if you want to try to find her, you can do whatever you want to, you know, she's really beautiful.
I just, yes, I just want to say that this is my girlfriend, yes, you can look for her.
I just want to tell you that I haven't nothing against American people. I
Just have it against the the state
Just like I don't like my this the
Mike
This person that you
No, this is my girlfriend. Oh
Wow
Well, what do you look like?
Uh, I want I want I won't show you myself
Because I want privacy, but I can show you her but if you want to look at her privacy
Because man, there's a lot of people that they hate me online
They was trying to dox me and trying to to find where I live
But now you're doxing your girlfriends. We thought you're down. You're doxing your own girlfriends. You are
But my girlfriend, she doesn't leave it with me.
She doesn't, you're using her photo,
going around YouTube panels, representing yourself.
What's going on here?
Are you doxing this woman?
Who is that?
This is my girlfriend, I'm telling you.
You're gonna tell her on the hand?
If you wanna try to look for her.
try to dox her or
Whatever you want to eat. I know I'm not going to I'm not going to but some other nut on the internet might want you not not like I'm a nut
But yeah, she's Brazil. She's Brazilian. She's Brazilian. She's my girlfriend. Okay. Well, I didn't tell your country she's from
You tell you you're giving away every all the information now
We have her country and we have a whole full photo and we have what her phone looks like
I can't show you her
No, don't tell me more you can't show any more your good dogs and your girlfriend stop
Okay
So what they never mind whatever she better not she better not she better not find out about this
Hello, so my real name is Jennifer my real name is Jennifer Martins
Okay, so now you're doxxing. Why are you doxxing yourself now? Yeah, why are you doxxing yourself? Honestly?
Guys, you know what's going on. Did you know what's going on? Is this something going on?
This seems like something strange. This is person
And is this an actress I
Am a knot I
Am a nut. Yes, you are. I mean there's one thing
just because she looks she looks beautiful you have any idea how many
beautiful girls I have in around me in my country how many a thousand a lot a
lot oh more than a thousand wow oh yeah Brazilians are beautiful let me see
okay people
Of course, if you if you look it up Brazilian models
There were the most famous and the most beautiful in Victoria's secrets in the US
There were the highest paid models and the most beautiful in the US
If you look it up
So it doesn't matter
If you believe me or not, that's a problem
So hey, so is that a thought of charisma Hernandez my mod my mod charisma Hernandez
I don't know I don't know I don't know why people
What is that charisma Hernandez charisma charisma
She's not my mod my my charisma. She must be my long-time long-time loyal friend
I can't tell you her name because you will be mad at me
I didn't ask for her name. I mean it is you it's charisma Hernandez
She says come on up charisma. Let's have the settles us. Let's settle this once and for all
I think summer is sponsoring
the chat tonight
Man, they would they want to leave me and I mean I'm gonna be posting summer summer as excellent as two channels
We have talk your ish and we have
They're so depressive
They're they're just to make you feel bad. They wanted to make you ugly
That they won't believe me. It doesn't matter what I say if I show the ugly picture
They would believe me, you know
But just because she looks good, they won't believe me. I know that
You know
So I don't really care. I don't give a shit
I can feel something inside me say I really don't think it's long enough
Sorry
So, no matter how hard I try, you keep pushing me aside, do you want to share?
I'm a very different for her.
And I'm not saying you are you share I'm gonna say you know, I know you're different like you know shares like a 50 year old or you know
And personality not not about looks but you my personality
We are very different, but she loves me. She really likes me. Let's go
But because I like to talk about geopolitics, history, and because I was in college, I was
studying history, theology, and all this stuff, and she's different.
She's more younger than me, and we are different, but we still love each other.
I'm really happy with her right now. She's really helping me to get over my exes, you know.
Well, you know, it's always good to have like, you know, somebody like, you know, like the person we love, you know
It's like, you know
Our soulmate like it's so nice to fight or at least you feel like that or at least at least a partner
But it's like I was at the same time. I didn't like being a relationship early. It felt smothering. It was like
Um, I still I feel like a lot lost too much freedom. Hey, good morning. I take it in the back for free
Oh, you're a trod. Who is but whose face is that? I recognize you. Hold on. Where are you from?
I see I've seen that face. Hey, do I know you? I don't know. You're just I've seen that face somewhere
Hmm
I don't care if you say I'm a boring but I have a beautiful girlfriend what you have
What do you have? I have a money. I have the money and a beautiful girlfriend. What do you have? Did I say you were boring?
I'd say you're boring. I
Said I have a money and a beautiful girlfriend. What do you have? I said, I don't
Say you're boring, I said you're like a little bit of a nut. No, I'm talking about the lady because
Okay, she's probably she's probably jealous because
My my girlfriend is beautiful that's right and she loves me
Okay, we don't need anything even hurt everything.
No, I'm saying the contrary.
Guys, I wanna thank Summer for sponsoring
the next three hours at least of a panel
because I will be running the panel and so...
You guys are welcome to come up. I'm going to pin the link in a second, but I'm going to change the banner
Don't be jealous. Don't be jealous
Americans, I know
America is in decline right now. Don't be jealous of okay
Because I know you explored
the third world that you call us in fear
but
now
The game is changing, you guys are gonna pay the karma for everything you have done.
To the poor people in the third world countries. You guys are gonna pay for okay
Don't threaten people like that. I mean, what are you talking about? Wait, what are you to say any of that?
We're not doing anything to anybody like what do we have to do with that?
I mean, it's like that now that's getting into like, you know, I don't like where it's going like there
It's like what are you talking about?
You know, you don't know anything about America. You don't live here. You don't keep America out of your mouth
You know, don't fuck with America. America is a fucking powerful country
Not like I'm saying we're bullying but it's like you know, don't think same crap about America
People all of a sudden thinking oh my god, he's allowing
Thank you. Yeah, what do you think? I mean, she was not interesting. Let them talk. What do you think you let them talk?
What do you want guys type of one in the chat? Should I bring her back up type of two?
I get you know, they're not worth it
She has like some other woman's picture up there. She's talking crazy about America and stuff
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. That's what random guy. That's what I was thinking. I was thinking
You know, that's the kind of like language that seems to me isn't that guys I don't like that
But yeah, no, it's obviously no. No, you don't wanna
Wow guys, wow, but everyone else is welcome on the panel and I will say you know, I'll be up here
hanging out with you and it's like, you know, summer if they
Kind of thought there's no one on the panel, you know, I'll either you know
We laugh at her little okay. Here we go
Hello Jennifer
Jennifer summer games summer gave you another chance
Okay, thank you. Thank you. Okay, but don't don't don't speak about like kind of like some of a Cassini a little bit like I like to kind of
What am I trying to say is that I don't need to live in the US to understand what's really going on
You just have to understand about geopolitics history
Economy right right
Okay, we're the people in this country. It's like so it's the people in the country. You know, we have limited
Like no ability to intercede on any of these things. We really we can't know this people think this people think I'm a boring
This people think I'm a barring because I talk about your politics politics and and I and they think they think that I am a
Disin America, you know, this is not the point
The point is about being it's I'm talking about facts
What's really going on? Yeah, well, what's going on tell me tell me tell me
What's really going on is that
The America Empire is in decline
This is the I don't want a history lesson. I don't talk about America. America's fine
Don't I'm not gonna talk about Brazil. You don't talk about America. Okay. We're I don't I don't live there
You don't live here. Okay, so let's just talk about our own countries. Okay, okay, okay if you don't want to talk the
I like to talk about that, but if you want to talk about something else, it's okay.
Wait, you're saying you're calling America as like this, this, this, this demon or something like that.
America is this evil place and that's like in Brazil, it's like, everyone's all nice and innocent.
Matt, if you want to, if you want to talk about something else, I can talk about it.
Okay, let's talk about something else.
So, what was the, tell me about a wild experience you had in your thirties, how old are you?
I'm 33.
33, oh wow, that's a great age, that's a great age.
I remember I was 33.
Yeah, what about you? What about you?
What am I? What am I whatever work?
How old are you? Oh, how am I I'm 44
Alright, yeah, okay, I look 44. They're like much much more handsome and younger
No, I don't I don't really care, you know
Do you want to do a reading tonight sweetheart? Or else that you know
I might want to like to say goodnight goodnight because I don't think that we have that much in common
Otherwise, but I'd like to make some cards on you see what's going on with you
What's going on with me, what are you in I can pull cards on you like a few cards tell you tell you what the energy is
So you can tell me that yeah, you can you can talk about it if you want to okay?
I'll do it. I feel I feel I feel it. I feel a good vibe. I'm just gonna drink all right
Okay, so let me get out the villains
Do you like this deck or
Oh
Okay
But I'm not saying you're a villain I'm saying that okay cool. It's a cool deck. Okay, so I'm shuffling the deck right now
They're just thinking about
My brother David. They do the same. Okay. Go ahead. He does tarot. He does tarot
Or blue head. Yeah, or is there some kind of like
Or there's another Brazilian religion, it's kind of hardcore, the Brazilian witchcraft.
No, there's not such a thing about Brazilian religion.
No, which are they going there for us in the forest they go in the forest
A secular state we have a lot of your religions in my country just like the u.s
Yeah, but there's like there's like this here
There's this crazy cult that lives in like the woods and like sets itself on fire and stuff
After after religions after religions. Yes. Okay. Okay. Yeah
Feel like they do a lot of voodoo
No, it's not that heavy, it's not that heavy.
Is it the black people that do it or is it all Brazilian?
It doesn't matter if it's black, is there black and white people?
Do black people consider themselves white in Brazil?
Of course not we we Brazilians just just like the USA
We were originally
indigenous land so
Portuguese Spanish Dutch Germans Japanese
We're all indigenous in the world, okay, so okay, I'm gonna pull three three car
I am I am actually white and half Italian in Portuguese
Okay. You are? Interesting. Okay. Oh, sure. Okay. Okay. Oh. Okay. Oh, wow. Okay. One more.
OK, this is the energy you're running, which is like the sine of cups energy.
OK, or the sine of cups.
So, the sine of cups.
It's like and you can see here. Well, here's Ursula here
So there's a lot there's a lot of energy in there and it's like a lot of emotion
But it's like and it's like almost and it's almost as if I ten of cups and it's like but you have to be careful when you get
Almost to that stage, you know, almost that stage of happiness and you ruin it by wanting wanting too much or something like that
But I would say for this nine of cups
This nine of cups says
Okay, so the nine of cups says
The tarot card is a very positive sign of success your wishes are being granted your lucky stars have aligned and
Things are finally falling into place. It's a time to enjoy yourself. Okay, so I hope things are open to happy time
You know, but it's like just remember. It's like, you know, you're you when you
The power can corrupt. Okay, so if you get some you got some more power or something that that
It's making you happy just be careful not to get you know, just remember what happened to Ursula. Okay. Oh, she's an occupant
Okay, so then I'm like am I looking around
Okay, what's so what's uh, what's
Above you and what's above you is goddess. You have some connections. Well, this is like the god. This is like the god card
It's the higher fit. He's comes. He's like a sheet
So this is like this purity. This is like this pure part of yourself and this is like this connection
That's in the that's in like the higher the higher above you
What's below you is like the nine of coins okay so nine of coins and this is like a money flow
you remember that's the thing it's like it's below you it's like you have to have
some I think it means you have to have your spending under control like you have to like
make sure that there's a money flow going and it's like and that you're also giving you know
spending to the right people and and bring putting your money out in the economy and stuff
I see in the past you would just have been getting over just like this like really big fight
You were fighting with a lot of people this is I can reverse and so like the fight is over
But it might have even gotten really bad at times, but I think it's I think it's been ending
It's been yeah, and then it's like in the future. It says it's the high priestess
Which is us in a it's Maleficent
I'll read this one the high priestess is all about using your own inner intuition because you have this intuition too
Maleficent and this high priestess is the number two card
Maleficent says that a high priestess is a secretive, intuitive figure whose power comes
from deep and from her own subconscious. Like Maleficent, she's sophisticated, calculating,
and a magical force to be reckoned with. The high priestess, Tara Card, is a call to look
deeper. You may not be seeing a situation, friendship, or relationship in your life for
what it really is. What is your intuition telling you?
Taking inspiration from mysterious maleficent and embrace solitude to ruminate on this predicament.
Consider it carefully, for there is more going on than meets the eye.
So hi, how was that? Hey Cam, how was that?
So guys if you'd like to come up for a reading too, that was her reading
I hope you like that reading but I mean in conclusion, it just means you know
It's a thing use your intuition about you can you know more than you think you know
You're probably psychic too and you have to have some abilities to abilities to
you know connect intuitively with people and in situations and be able to
Find your own powers too, right? We all have powers
You just have to
You know be thankful for them and all gifts, right?
So I
Believing in intuition. What do you think of the what you think of the reading though?
Was that was that the pride resident at all? Was that they get any points, right? Or anything really really wrong you can tell yourself? I
Don't know. I don't know. It's uncertain, but I believe in my intuition but
I believe in Jesus Christ in the Bible.
Sure.
Jesus never said anything bad about, you know, no tarot cards or anything.
Tarot cards are not even mentioned in the Bible.
But they do mention fortune telling.
I don't consider it fortune telling, I consider it just like, you know, soul searching
and getting to know, I think this is the era where we're going to get to know ourselves.
All the information is all out there.
We're supposed to know thyself, that's the most important thing, right?
People will tell you what you are, tell you who you are, put you in boxes, put you in jackets, put you in labels.
You're not what people say you are and you're not even, we're not even the same people day to day.
Our mind is so complicated and there's so many places in the,
I wonder that we're able to focus on one thing at a time at all.
Because there's so many things going on millions of things pulling at us in different directions trying and we have to figure out all this stuff
It's amazing that we're able to do it. It's actually making order from chaos and that's what we're actually doing it
That's what that's what that's what my life feels like. It's just feels like order from chaos
It feels like everything's going wrong, but somehow it's like everything's
Stable, I don't know. It's like I get really worried when everything goes, right?
then they're about to go wrong but most things are going wrong it's like that's life and then yeah
i love you guys i'm gonna post the link in the chat
This is gonna be open. Oh, yeah, so I also wanted to put the banner up for summer
So guys, okay, thank you summer for sponsoring the panel until 11 30
P oh not 11 30
The time will be 11 30 11 to 12 12 12 12. It's a 2 a.m. 2 a.m. Okay, and
So that will be open till 2 a.m. It's open right now
This will just help keep it keep it limited. It will help to keep it. It's like exclusive
It was just it was just like I think the people on the panel will look out more for the people to be like
Respectful and you know on the show because you know, I think a lot of them
But I want to say so so thank you summer for sponsoring the panel until 2 a.m. PS the big standard time
subscribe
To I'm gonna put the names of your channels
Summer and then if my can like post the link in the chat hot mess summer and
Talk your ish
Okay, so there I'm gonna now do this for anybody that will like you know is a
Would like to have their you know your show
Being promoted my banner whatever
Because she donated for the show tonight, so there you go summer I'm gonna post a new new color to have a nice purple
My girlfriend lives in Brazil she doesn't need to go to the USA, okay?
She lives in my country. We have a we still have the beautiful safe clean
developed cities here
Brazil is not only about slums about the ghetto
Violence they organize crime. We have a beautiful cities here
I'm just I'm just answering the the the people on the chat. I'm sorry
No, it's okay. I apologize, you're doing something wrong. You're fine. I'm sorry to interrupt you
Because some people need some foreigners they think that Brazil
It's the country. Brazil is the most the same size of the U.S., the most the same size of the U.S.
So, we have a different reality in my country.
In the south, we are more developed. I live in the south of my country, the southern.
And here we are more developed, we have beautiful clean cities, we have missions, we have beautiful
nice cars, we have security, it's not only because they think Brazil is only about slums,
crimes, all this bullshit, they don't even know what they're saying, because this is
Of course, we have our issues, there's a lot of social inequality, because we are not a developed country.
We are not a developed country, unfortunately, because we could be, but the government, the US and the government, our government, won't allow us to be a developed country.
Because we could be we have oil we have a natural resources. We have we have everything we have we are the eternal largest
We we we produce food for for for the whole world
You know we have we could become a superpower
There isn't that we don't come don't we don't become a superpower. It's because
There's a bunch of oligarchs on the government
They pretend to be a democracy, but just like the US
They are a bunch of oligarchs. It's a billionaires. They they're they're just people is starving
leaving on the street
And
It is ridiculous, you know
Because we could be
This is the problem
The problem is this
Bullshit, hey, I'll talk to you later
How annoying anyway guys, I just over five memberships to you guys
I think we got some five members five new members. Okay classy sassy welcome zimpulse welcome garth hooks
Elsa, four, and Boston Strong, six, one, seven,
you all got a free membership.
Guys, you know what you get when you get a free membership?
Because they're $5, right?
$4.99, okay?
You get access to over 100 videos.
Some of them are over eight hours long of past shows.
Oh, we have the classic shows.
I'm gonna put all my videos on members only from now on too.
And so you'll have access to those.
You'll have a special, oh yeah, Barbara, yep.
You'll get a, just members only once a week.
I'm gonna show you every Sunday, probably,
a couple hours, just for members to talk
and do some readings for members and just have a chat
and just have a little more of an intimate member,
you know, just for the members.
And then,
There's emojis, do you guys see the cool new emojis?
Look at the emojis for members too, guys.
So if you can click on the join,
you can like do some like eyes,
and then you can like do like maybe,
I have this one that's like the gong and you're like,
oh, take it, if you wanna like kick somebody off,
you can like do the gong, oh, hold on one second.
Yo.
That was great. You heard that idiot ramble gone about Brazil becoming a good country and you're like
I can't hear this bullshit and you kicked them. Yeah, kick their off. Yeah, that was bullshit lady. I see it
Brazil ain't going nowhere. We don't give a fuck about Brazil. All right. Thanks for letting me on see you
Of course, I
mean
But yeah, I don't mind Brazil, you know, I mean, I love Brazil. It's just like
She's annoying. But anyway, so when you so when you type those in the chat
Like I will see actually see something so I'll see the words on my screen because it comes out as words on my thing
Like it looks like this like see just go go go. So
But I'll see it and so I have some of them that are set up for like see this one says
SOS
This one says
Like crystal ball if you want like a reading you can do that. It would be my attention. You're like, I'm here for chaos
I'm here for trouble. Just you do this one. It's like a skull. I'm gonna have to redo that one because it's not perfect
Okay, and then it's like a
And if you like when I like say I'm a vampire you go like that. I'm a vampire and then if you want to say like
I'm gonna go on and say oh
What does that say? It says like LOL you can say oh
It's so funny
It's my, it says LOL, it's poor mongering against the rules.
Yes, they turn, unless, unless you like, unless it's like you
and we're backstage and we're having a ditty party
and I rubbed all the oil, baby oil on you
and then I was sucking your dick off camera.
That's the only way.
Are you a vampire prince?
Do I look like one?
I could take a vampire prince photo.
Guys, we're gonna do also this really cool video
of Gaudi and me.
Oh, hold on.
Hello darling. Hey Scythe, how are you doing? Yeah, how are you sweetie? Great
So what's been going on? I miss a lot
Yeah, you know lots been going on. It seems like
You know, it's a cruel cruel cruel sudden man
Leaving me here on my own, it's a crew.
Actually, the show's going great.
I clean my house today.
My house, I feel like a new person.
I really do.
It's like, I feel like the snake has shed its skin.
Also, it's Friday, so.
Yeah, oh, yeah.
I love fucking love Fridays.
I'm thinking of getting some kind of coffee or something.
I'm going to make kind of like.
Some kind of coffee.
They have the coffee in the middle of the night.
They probably put Jack in the box or something.
Oh
Damn, thank you. There's some good coffees. I say Taco Bell has a good Cinebun coffee here. Had that one
Yeah, no way you'll do it Max. Well, how's that fancy shit? No, I just don't
You think oh, I mean my own own. Oh, you do cowboy coffee or here a cowboy coffee. Yeah
It's like just put the grounds in the fucking
the thing.
Hey, yeah, it's just a little drink of grats.
Delicious.
Yeah, I miss you.
I miss everything you miss you.
You're here.
Thank you for being here.
My show is still here.
Can you believe it?
Remember when I thought the show would be gone?
You thought that all the time.
The entire time you had your show.
I didn't know.
We were so bad.
Did you see how you saw this thing?
Hi, Jamie
No, I haven't seen that but thank you for the nightmares
I'm kidding nightmares
That's right. That looks at me while I sleep. I put it. That's what my that's why I'm dead
Okay
It makes me feel it makes me feel so self-conscious. I don't even want to jerk off anymore because I feel like I'm being washed
I'm being washed by unseen forces
No, there's your first problem. I mean sleeping next to it. That's number one
Jerking to it probably to I'm not sure no
I'm not jerking to the alien or to the kitten and I've been talking about the aliens just watching me and so I
Wouldn't do that. I wouldn't do that because there's an alien in a kitten there. I wouldn't do that
so they're like god or gods you see their eyes well they're not well the aliens maybe they're
like people in scuba outfits i don't i don't know what the fuck they are i mean i don't know maybe
they're like those furries or cosplayers or like you know it's power rangers who i don't know what
Don't know. Anyway, I like I like the cats. So I love the cats. They gave me maybe the best cat. They're so magical
Jamie do you want to hear the gaudi song you got you right here's a gaudi song
I made a gaudi song. Did you just hurt you just met him tonight, right? No. Oh, you know him before no
Okay. Well, here's the gaudi song
I'll play right now
Out of New York came a storm on wheels
Rollin' in smooth with the mafia feels
Cuban cigar lit like it's temper
Pizza in one hand, hot dog for dinner said psyche
I'm bored, had to switch the scene
Left some poor woman screamin' on live stream
Trolled her down to the void and back
Then crashed my show like a heart attack
Gotti, main man, troking
But they're still my friends
Yeah, love, you got it
Till the bitter end we fight
We troll, but we friends
Forever my friend
You're a lover. You're a lover.
You can't hear it? Oh, it's there.
Hold on. Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. I'll tell you where. I'll tell you where.
With the lowercase g in a wheelchair
still stomping through the live feed
bow to your king while smoking that leaf
laughing at chaos like it's comic relief
brought spunky two now that trolls a gem
mean one sweet ones they all jumped in
cameras glitching chat on fire
mods begging me to cut the wire
But nah, I like my circus, I love this mess
Every troll's just a test, stop the mess
Gotty a rude, absurd and free
But deep down you got loyalty
Gotty made man, troll king
Off the assault, rolling through
Panels like he's in control
Discorn army, Amish Italian
Mormon plan, they dangerous wild
But they still mad
But we friends forever my friend. Yeah
Then defended my clown
Spam my chat and held it down
You got layers like a deep dish slice
Under all that shade a
Heart made of ice
rice so let's light that cigar raise the mic another night of chaos welcome to
psych you brought the drama the heat the fun and weirdly it feels like you're the one
got it yeah you crazy but your family now rolling through fire still taking a bow no matter
I know it's a play, I'm sorry, I'll take it off.
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on,
hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on,
hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold
on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold
Okay, it's fine. It's fine. You don't have to it's it is a special. So I think God got a God God got a church who is I
Wouldn't hurt that song and I did too
But anyway, you I know you're not you're on a sentiment. I'm a little I'm like the little sentimental bitch
Call it say it to me say to me. It's calm to call me please get your aggression. Use your chance right now
Yes, thank you so much. Oh, thank you. We're even we're so even
Remember I called you that I thought so bad I was like oh my god I called her a bitch
And I was like it's all word. I was like she's gonna hate me
I was so trippin about it, and then I talked the next day, and I was like I'm sorry you're like what?
Yeah, I don't care you call me a bitch you faggot
Technically you didn't call me a bitch. I know I knew you didn't call me that I mean I was just a joke
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm a little bit. I'm a little bit happy lately. I'm a little bit crazy or something
I'm just going going insane. Oh
Who's got you smile like that?
Love interest in your life. Hmm. I wish
Well, I really don't it's like every time I
They the people I'm attracted to are too dangerous to date. They're like
Criminals they're like game members criminals
People that way they
Have me chalk chopped up. Do you got mad at me and we had one argument?
Like Barbara fake rumor that I tickled around it lying about that's what you guys talking about that chat. That's it's weird
Yeah, there was a love letter to God. Hey, I think I thought it was a cute that I thought it was a cute song
I mean, I tried to make it realistic and stuff like
But it's true. It is true. He's a nice person. I got along with him
Some of the other people know I love spunky though spunky
But it's spunky to copy that uh, this uh, this neon thing that it always just reminds me
Aliens are watching you if you don't fuck up
Okay, there is my Hernandez. What's up princess Lee? How about you don't use okay?
I don't know you guys are talking about you guys are just talking about nonsense in the chat, but anyway, I
Know what it will Jamie so
What you've been up to like what where have you been you've been in my a
Yeah, your boyfriend. How's your boyfriend? You have a boyfriend, right? Or have a boyfriend husband
Congratulations, thank you
Hello, Mary. Oh, you're married before
Has even
Were you married before like were you married recently or like?
I just I just had met him one time. I bet so I thought he was kind of new
Yeah, no
He's cute. Yeah, he's a good listen. Oh, I don't know if he's cute. He had a cute voice
Variants
It sounded like a cute person
Or like a tell I don't know but sometimes you know when you call tell you call like a business and there's like a person on the phone
They're like hello, and they're like they have the nicest voice
And I bet they're like hot and then it's like if you were to see them they're like 500 pounds and they're like, you know
No, he's hot
Yeah, yeah, no, I thought that before for sure. Okay. Yeah, but yeah
Extremely. Oh, yeah, I'm sure I know I know he's hot. I know he's hot. I'm saying yeah
Sometimes sometimes the voices that could be deceiving so I didn't know but I take your word for it. You are hot
Yeah, so I will put you in a I'll put you in a AI song soon, Jamie
We have some kind of we have some kind of drama or conflict you but you fought with Florida diamond, right?
You know, she's dating raging demon now
I don't know her raging demon is not up top my head
Think pretty diamond should be dating Alex. You know if you on my opinion as a matchmaker as a professional matchmaker
I think Alex
And what is it? Yeah, the fake cop Alex should be dating 30
Well, what are you doing? What is that?
Palm crisps for cheese
It's like little cheese crispy thing. Hey, I was gonna show you I was surprised for you. I'm dating somebody. I
Have the video of our our first meeting right here
I fell I fell
I didn't fall you fell. Oh, oh the phone fell
Are you gonna see what happened? You won't believe it. Don't believe it, right?
Work right easy, huh? Did it look
Beautiful
I like the one of Jimmy
There's one Jimmy kissing Deacon. Oh, that's a good look at this one. Look at this one
He's a he's a dwarf and she's a giant that one
Anyway, that's pretty cool. Do you like that guys? I
like
Hmm, have you ever had Deacon up here? I don't think so. Can you get him on the show? Thank you. I could
He's in his dick cat. He's in his dick cat. His name is Deacon. He's now just like this and he's gonna call you a god damn cool
My best my best impersonation of him
You god damn cool
Is that like Ernest? Hey, Ernest, Ernest!
Armini cheese
Hmm
We didn't even know he's gay now. I think I'll figure out when his dicks when he's sucking Lordy Devon's dick
Well, he's got his fingers up his butt
I think so
What do you think Jamie?
I don't think you do. Well, you figure it out. I don't know if he knows Lordy Devon's
Of course, I haven't got
Never got me in trouble because forty seven started stroking this balloon animal. She had under her pants
I don't know what it was. He's there was he's used a penis pump or something on his on his dick
I don't know what he did, but I'll know as he got the video taken down
YouTube saying
What the fuck was that? So I can never had a banner for the time being well, all I know is that you acted like
Fucking what what's what's his government name by the way? What's 30 diamonds rule fucking name?
Jorge Jorge Jorge Valenza Jorge Valenza I didn't like the fact that you kept this little
Jig up like it was a woman the whole fucking time you're like
And I love to fool I love to fool people you straight people are evil
No, I mean, I'm evil you shape people. I'd like to fool you with drag queens and get your all confused
chaos
Okay, sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Are you done? No. Yes, Sam
First of all, I thought we were friends baby. You're friends. Hey sweetheart. I was just kidding. He is a friend. What'd I do?
You were trying to pull the wool over my eyes. You try to make that
free pubic and boy
Was a woman. He's not. He's 22 23 years old
So that adult man was a woman. Yes. I mean just I mean I didn't figure it out for like
Ten minutes. It took me like ten minutes to figure out. No, I'm just kidding. No
I really didn't like written register that he that she was a male the first time I met her like I thought
Oh, I thought it was a female
But then I was on Samans and they were playing a clip and you're like, hey
It's like you think it's a guy or a girl and I was like what the I think of course it's a guy
I was I mean it's like it was like
They knew there was something like off or you know, but I say I just couldn't I don't really care
It's not a big it's not a moral thing or any
Was it the voice pack or the clip wherever he like fell over the table, and then they're fucking winged
It was an it was his nipples. I mean it's the nipples. They're like a male nipples. I mean
I don't know. This is a you seem like mailed. I mean, I love you. Sorry diamond. I don't know if you don't shave
But it's like if they look like
That's what I always they look like, you know chocolate shit pancakes like sewn on to the
Like a big mountain Jell-O. I don't know it's just but now it's for you guys
I think it's sober right now and congratulations, and I wish you best of the Friday and
All is forgive it. If you forgive me, I'll forgive you, you know
But I'm gonna do enough. I'm gonna like I'm gonna thank you enough for the diamonds to like make us even
Fucking getting in trouble with YouTube
It's like she's like the babysitter. It's like you never hire like this crazy
Transsexual as a babysitter right because she come over the fucking get drunk on the couch. The baby will be you know
Hopefully like still in the house. You know and not, you know, you're sold to Mexico or or like, you know, you know
Fallen up for you know gotten hurt or something and then
Come home. You're like, why would I hire flirty diamond as a babysitter?
This woman wants a flirty diamond wants to have a hysterectomy not hysterectomy. She wants to have a uterus implant
so that she can get pregnant so that she can have an abortion does that make any sense to you that
sounds like some kind of sick lot some sick thinking to me well you know i think starting
the issue is hiring a uh what's it what's the name again a transvestite
transsexual oh transsexual babysitter like how about just a babysitter how i just do that
Yeah, that's what I'm saying
What are all these names?
And I know I'm saying okay. Well, but I'm saying well, they actually do do
Drugs like these do these hormones and the hormones will change you significantly, right?
Not give you the the breast because those those breasts are natural breasts from the hormones. That is amazing
I'm a very how about how about you try some and tell us your experience. I
Don't feel like becoming a woman. I know you'd be pretty. It would hurt. I would have a period
You're not gonna carry it away. I'd have a period every day
A thousand woman. I mean, I've got to open wounds. Are you serious?
Hello
Why are you laughing? No, I'm just very funny
I'm a funny man
You're a funny girl. You're a cool chick. Thank you
Funny woman. Maybe friends forever, Jamie
Yes, until the day I die
Okay, if you if I were getting trouble about it, I mean if I ever have people after me and something like that
Can I sleep in your basement?
Basements, there's no basement in Texas. Do you have an attic?
Give a bar
That's another reason she does she she has a barn
Okay, well, it's okay. I'll just peace. I'll find her bar and I'll sleep in the barn
I'm just okay, I can go in the park. I think I'm just I'm just kidding. I'm not gonna not gonna go to your bar
I'm fine. I am. I'm very happy. I'm a
I'm a lucky guy as they say
Lucky guy. Why only 43 minutes? I know I need at least like I need at least an hour and a half with Jamie Rose
Can we change it to that 90 minutes with Jamie Rose? I?
Really want to take the whole 43 minutes away was like an inside joke and
Are you pass now? It's okay
Along with Marty all right. Oh, I'm sorry. Yeah, or if you Marty and I know but it's like, you know, like isn't it like a
Nice to remember sometimes or
I know it hurts, it hurts, it just hurts, but it's nice to remember people.
I don't know it's nice, but then it's not because like and I've never received any signs from him
Because you have a you haven't you really haven't had a dream or anything like not a thing
So I've I've had a dream about Marty and about you like a few a couple times
But I mean it's like it we were like we were running around doing like some fun stuff
And it's like it seemed like he was still alive. It was like very like it was just like we were just like happy
Just like it was like, you know, it's like I think like
We can be like in these different like happy states, you know, I don't know. I think maybe this I don't know if that's him
Or it's my memory or something, but I've driven drows
And and you're my reality too has Jimmy been in prison. Have you been in prison?
No, he is like the sex the sexy like typewriter person
Having the police reports. No, she's not been in prison. I don't have
The jail have been the jail. No, have you gotten a speeding ticket? Yes. Oh
criminal. No, she's fine. Yeah, I've got like, wow. Oh my God. But I get let go of on majority.
You ever say, you ever say, let's take care of this, like, you know, how you know, Alex and I did
when he pulled me over and I was like, hey, do you want to go to the bushes instead? No. I mean,
I even asked actually, he just threw me the bushes. And then, there's something real bad.
And then you know what happened then Jamie Rose. Do you remember what happened next? No, I don't
Alex
What are you gonna do to me if I you pull me over and I've been speeding on the freeway
What are you gonna do to me? I'm gonna say sir
Registration I'm gonna pretend it's bad. I'm gonna say step out of the car and I'm gonna throw you in the bushes
In the bushes, I'm gonna fuck the shit out of you. In the bushes, okay?
Oh my gosh.
In the trees, on the side of the highway, I'm gonna fucking just give it to you.
And then that's it, my man. I'm gonna make popcorn and just go on my way.
Mm-hmm. Well, you know, even though that was very funny, that makes me think that Alex
Say it, say it, son of a bitch.
We'll have a moment. We'll have a moment. No, are we all like don't we all just like a sad like, you know
Like a person inside somewhere in our psyche are we are we all these are we everybody are we all these people?
Isn't that didn't you ever didn't you ever feel like that? Like we are everybody like we're just like everybody's like really the same person
But in all these different bodies and everyone thinks they're different
But it's like we're actually all the same, but we're all different. I guess and maybe have a better vocabulary
All right, I'm sorry.
It's okay, no, no, no.
Jamie, I love you.
You know, I know you're abrasive and you're harsh and you're like, you know, a little
bit mean sometimes, but, you know, you're okay.
I can handle it.
You're like the most beautiful troll princess I've ever seen in my life.
Troll American princess. It's called a tap a tap your tap not a Jewish American person. You're a troll. I know the Japas
Japanese Japanese person definitely the Japanese
So where's where's beta?
You know it was here this morning. Yeah, be do us here this morning
I said this guy. This is Jewish guy named Moshe after me. He's saying oh every he's like oh and
He's like he's like unite with your enemy to fight against psyche. Like I'm like the fucking antichrist or something
I know who Moshe is
Well, can you talk to him and tell him to come the fuck down? I'm not like oh, I cannot I
Unfortunately, I cannot Moshe X has a thing for me
Because he thinks I'm not
Native Native American
He's just got this Vendetta isn't your name is your name Jamie Pocahontas Rose
No, I thought that was your middle name, so it's not but you know let him dig it's funny
But I don't I don't just like motion
I think it's I mean, I don't like second me either
But he's on he's on Kate's talking shit about me in the chat
Like I'm not like sitting there monitoring her chat because like half the comments are about me there
Oh, and they're always it's outrageous accusations. Oh psych. This guy's like, oh, I do say I do psyche like you're 2020
And he was with his me and the RV and I was like I was never I was in on into like last year
So people just making stuff up and there's like, I'm sure I have pictures and I say there's making things up
When was the last time you played there? You sharded Jamie? Like what was the last time? I don't know.
Jamie, don't answer that. That's not a question for a lady.
Oh yeah, don't answer that. No, I'll answer whatever I want.
Okay, I don't want to hear the answer. Wait, when was the last time I sharded,
sharded like shit in my pants? Well, you actually, yeah, I thought we were gonna fart and then
more came out. Yeah, I would say I was probably eight years old and I had to go to the
This was actually a sad story
Last time you never done it since that I mean
Never does an adult been blessed. I mean, I just did it this morning. I mean, it's like oh, I'm just kidding
It got I'm just good. God. I'm not kidding. I am I am I don't I don't sharp myself
I really don't I have actually my my my stool is very firm right now because I've been having a good meeting a lot of fiber
But I have don't really want to get on this topic
Are you only here more so I'll tell you about I want to tell you about the color
I'm just kidding when you're talking you're right to answer
The question
I'm just kidding. You know what that means. I'm an asshole. No, I said you're giving me asco
Do you know what Oscar?
Oscar, what does that mean? It means like I want to throw up
Oscar
You be mean to me now
No, Oscar means you weren't yeah
You want to throw up? That's what that means. Oscar means throw up. I'm sorry. Why do you want me make you throw up?
I don't want you to throw up. I'm telling you. I'm sorry make you say I'm not gonna say I'm not gonna say it again
I'm sorry. Okay, great. Sorry. I'm sorry, Jamie. You're I know would make you upset. Dude, don't cry
You crying. Yeah
I
Have to call me Oscar the Grouch stop it. There's so mean
I'm sorry me to cry
So that's a 40-diamond actually call me Oscar the Grouch
She said I was like Oscar the Grouch. I look like a little bit of trash. Yeah, do you see my house?
I did my beautiful house. Well, look at this beautiful house. Look
That's my lover right there
It's an alien.
The alien, he's actually 3,000 years old, okay?
I mean, it's like, fuck.
Talk about an age difference.
But he's a really nice guy.
Well, or a woman.
I'm not sure.
He has like three sets of genitals.
And anyway, and the cat's really cool too.
It's like this pink neon cat.
If you touch it, it will like burn, you know,
burn off your hands.
I can only look at it from afar, but it's very cute.
Hello?
I'm not crying. I'm not crying. I'm like I'm like laughing I'm like laughing so hard that it's
Manifesting into visible tears running down my face
I'm just kidding
You're good
Oh, you're muted
Hello
You were you were muted. I mean, I know thank God because my phone kept falling on the floor
It's where the fall over again
Jamie can you eat a banana for world peace for the chat? Yeah, that'd be great
Can you eat a banana?
How much of a donation could someone give me for you to eat a banana on the stream?
Let me read the chat. What is the chance? They're asking you to eat a banana
I think well, I just don't like the name
How about a piece pickle a pickle a pickle? I love pickles. Yeah, well, there we go. Okay. Now. Okay guys
How about a pickle eating contest between me and you? Oh?
I think every every every twenty dollars someone would send us we would eat a pickle a big one
Yeah, one bite one one bite and then we would bet it would be like how many or that we eat the most it would just be like
How many could you eat well? I look at you right now and say you take a whole boat load
I can't I can't why I can you tell you one pick
What's that? I can you a one big pickle. I can eat one big pickle just I wouldn't
But I want to gherkin I want to get a little like the little smaller. No, I know two pickles. No, no
We need the big daddies
You're gonna get the black the black guys we need the black guys the black black black eyed peas
No, let's let's you know what I don't like pickles anymore. I don't think how about let's
Let's grow cucumbers, you know 30 diamond ones for a cucumber in her butt, and it came out of pickle
What's so funny I'm just listening
I don't think that's true the other way that that never happened. I've never yeah, that was it's called parody satire
30 diamond. It's actually a
satire of a
woman I
Think I don't know. I don't know what the fuck she is. She's an enigma. It's the turn
No, I like 30 I like 30 diamond. I'm just saying 40 diamond. Don't cut it off. You know, just keep it on
you don't want to fuck him be putting a
Stents dildo and for the rest of your life like having this
Dressing you know how much we're gonna spend on adhesive gauze. I mean, it's nightmare
At that point I'll just I'll just call it a day and donate all my all my other organs to science
Like 30 diamond like he what's his name again our ratio
Or or hey Gonzalez for it. Okay. So like Jorge wants to like chop it, right? Jorge said fuck this dick
I want to just
Knob it right the fuck off, right? He doesn't want no, he doesn't want to be she doesn't want to but I mean she doesn't want to
But I think she's insane
So yeah, you know, you made a lot allowed to do it. Okay, but the
This year, but it's a 20 grand and it's like it's a decent one. Let's you go to Mexico
You know what the two brands it's your own chop the flop
Okay, fine. Stay. She does say she doesn't what about the other issues face her face her body
No, she has a pretty passable, passable face.
She has a body.
She has her body, her body's a little bit like, you know,
safe of marshmallow, man, but the rest of her looks pretty, pretty, uh,
the body. Yeah, authentic torta.
The torta? You like the torta? You like the little dessert? The torta?
What do you? No, she needs to go to the gym.
He needs to go to the gym.
For your diamond, I hope you, please come, please come.
Yeah, I would be bothered to talk to for your diamond, actually.
That fat puta.
She could get a chopped off methi in prison.
But yeah in prison you can because the guys can go into the women's prison if they if they get a sex change
They can if they want to but why would you want to go to women's prison?
I mean it is nicer for like the you know what they all they do is they comb each other's hair and fucking, you know
You know like it's in kumbaya, but you know, it's
Probably better than the men's prison unless you're like really the anal sex. I'm not really but I would probably be a daddy
I try to be a daddy you choose Rusty over Slayer in you any day
Rusty I don't even know who these people are
Oh, you're talking to somebody in the chat. I'm sorry. Sorry. I'll say it. I'll say it
Okay, anyway
Jamie, how is it? How is it just being like such as like I know you mug every place you go, right?
Don't you mug every place you go?
You know what that means?
Doing Mark. Yes, you mugged every place you go, right? Yeah, I guess I
Agree, I think you probably are the most beautiful woman every place you go. Isn't that awesome feeling not really
Why not? I don't like attention
Jake be like being ignored
No, I don't like that either, but I just
But I don't think you will get a lot of attention. I mean you'll get a lot of old men coming up to you asking for your phone number and like talking
You'll get like
I don't know it depends on where you are like I'm just thinking of Alisa where she's in the middle
It was Florida where it's like all these like old men and she just gets fly like flies to honey like
Like hey, mommy. They're all gonna they don't give a shit if you look like a Lisa or you
Or a fucking half-dead fly I gotta go down there. How about how about well?
Don't say what why that's that's very nice. Oh, Alisa you or a half-dead fly
That's what you that's our this is grouping you put us into like it's like at least in me and a half-dead fly
The same shit to all y'all
Like hey, let me see you move your little leg. I'll say the next one. Yeah, it's in my brain
Move your leg
We go we go
Dale
The fly would start to read our name
and started no dance, then it would wake up and the passing man would be, he'd feel complete
and then you would have been as well. Problem solved. Dali.
Are you done? I am done. Good.
Anyway, you know, I thought Jamie Rose is a cool person. She's the match is like muttering these Mexican curses to me under her breath
And being really cruel. I don't know what why she's turning into such a mean mean person
Why why turn on me Jamie Rose? Why I just turn on me like that turn me like that
It's like that like that like this like this like this one second one second one second
What was it? It's one second. I'll just turn on you one second
Every I was gonna turn on you so it's her on you
It was always like that, wasn't it?
Jamie Rose
Never trust a rose. They have thorns
sharp ones
and I'm
Rosalind smell that good anyway as I prefer the orchids or the
Lilacs or the Crocus. Mr. Sensen, it was really annoying today
You think American came from where? Usually indigenous land colonized by
Europeans I guess
Anyway, I'm just kidding. I'm sure I'm just kidding. Well, why we always fight what we always I start fights in January
Well, I feel like we're dating sometimes and they don't even get the, you know, the
I don't I feel like I'm dating but I never get the nice version of the person. I always get the mean version
Take my wrench away for granny. Who's granny? Don't call don't call people names. You mean he's not granny
What are you talking about? Oh, yeah, you mean hold on. Hey, can I say the N word up here? Can I say nerve?
I love you, Jamie. Good night, sweetheart. I hope Jamie has a great night
I hope she like has a fun night, and I hope I never see her again. Bye. Okay, so
Anyway, that was really inappropriate guys
I really want to apologize if there's anybody of any any other race that has heard that and then it's like, you know
Just her saying that like that
You'd like her already. Well, yeah, she go find her. Yeah, this is a girl that loves the animal, right?
I was saying I was kidding around there. She actually took it things way too personally. Why'd she get so
I don't know what just happened. She she turned full
David Duke on me. She really did. You know, I don't know
She's a she's a Mexican clan member basically, right?
That's that's what she is
Anyway, I love you, Jamie Rose. Talk to you later.
I try, I was trying to get there on time. Oh my god, right? Evil, what a evil evil woman, Jamie Rose.
You're just Vader's type. His Vader's black, but he likes being called the Unmort, right?
You are black. Are you black? Are you not? That's as black as it gets. It looks like to me.
Are you talking to me? Oh, thank you a little better better. I'm a male guy
Yo estoy un hombre. Why is everyone so touching with the n-word? Just because it's against the key word
I don't know. I just don't like you know, is like if you really use it too much and she was like
But she was just like saying it in a rude way like what that's it
That's the next topic of conversation
She can like give it back to you in other ways it doesn't say and I say the n-word and just like saying something so lazy
The n-word is just lazy
The panel's on over. We have another couple hours if anyone wants to come up
I'm hanging out
If no one wants to come up, I mean, of course I have like, you know, I can read I can read that book 28 people in the chat
You want to you to interview destiny will destiny to a comeback but destiny was being a weirdo, I mean it's like again I
Don't want I don't want to talk about these like
Political stuff people keep bringing up. Okay, so I'm gonna read this. I'm gonna start reading this book. It's called the cop
It's called you need a card. Okay. I got the
One card got even number gotty
Yeah, she's a normal she saw I'll forget I forgive her she'll probably forgive me
Oh, that's what we're like for like my brother sister working like go fuck you and then we're like friends again
Okay
Wow good, I just got a smell I'm getting like a really sweet smell all of a sudden
I don't know what that's from but it's like I'm really like I don't know if that's it's kind of psychic thing
But I'm smelling kind of musky, okay, but it's not like sweet. They got cologne two three
Okay
Got it a of cups. Okay, so here we have this eight of cups and this eight of cups
You'll notice he has like he has almost this complete set. I don't know
You can see though these nice cups, but there's a look you can see there's one missing from the set
You know, he's gonna go. I don't know what would happen to that cup, but he's gonna go look for that cup. Okay
But don't forget like you're
Leaving all your don't just keep an eye on everything you have and don't like leave too long and also
It's a pretty nice set already, you know, I say but I don't know you're gonna want to go for the 10 of cups
You're everyone said 10 of cups. It's like you have so much. So just remember you have a lot
A lot of uh emotional strength a lot of emotional strength and you're gonna get to the 10 of cups
It's probably even closer than you think
We probably don't even have to do anything bad to get it. I think I think this one is the one you need to get
I'm good terms. Okay, so I hope you like that you click McDonald's Batman forever cuffs. That's pretty cool
Hope you enjoy that
Okay, so I'm gonna try to tell you about this story. So this is called the comp day de Gabales
Okay, it's by a bay and a month who can devilar
Okay
So this is a very esoteric work. Okay. Oh, you're welcome. I hope you like that. It says okay
So this is a picture. Okay, so I have actually meditated. I would do this thing called the middle the middle pillar, okay?
It's a cobblistic
Meditation and you like basically call these different frequencies into different chakras, right?
And I would do this regularly. I was very into like I want to open my third eye
Whatever and so this is what I saw in my brain. This is what I saw in my brain
I don't know if you can see it. That's what I pretty much saw and it's like a guy
It's like a he's wrapped in like this like a serpent right there. You can kind of see
Anyway, I would I would really that's what I saw when I would like close my eyes after a little while and so
It says, this ancient monument of the mysteries portrays the action of the solar flame in
and about the God-enlightened man.
When governed and directed upward, the flame becomes an instrument which the soul uses
to build up the deathless solar or spiritual body.
Okay, so it says, invocation to the flame. It says, I call upon thee, O living God, radiant
with illuminating fire. O unseen parent of the sun, pour forth thy light, giving power
and energize thy divine spark. Enter into this flame, and let it be agitated by the
breath of thy Holy Spirit. Manifest thy power, and open for me the temple of Almighty God,
which is within this fire. Manifest thy light for my regeneration, and let the breath
height, fullness, and crown of the solar radiance appear, and may the God within shine forth."
It says, warning, this book is about the student who seeks to illuminate his intelligence by the
torch of his own divinity, that him whose quest is the gratification of a selfish intellectualism
beware its pages, for this book is of hidden mystery and power. Therefore, let the mind be pure,
that it may invite the approach of a pilgrim soul to come into a new realization of the
interesting. Okay, goes into a little history, but I'm gonna keep the history
kind of a mystery right now. History is kind of like not the most
important thing to me. It's actually the message, okay. So, are you guys interested?
Well, I'll read you this a little bit. So it says, La Comte de Gabales, and you can
Are there pictures?
Free equal.
So it says, May the soul of the comte de Gabelis be now in the presence of God, for they have
just written me that he has died of apoplexy.
The amateurs will not fail to stay in this manner of jets usually befall those who deal
unconsciously with the secrets of sages, and as since the blessed Raymond Lully, so decreed
in his testament, an avenging angel has never failed promptly to ring the necks of all who
have indiscreetly revealed the philosophic mysteries.
but let them not condemn this learned man thus hastily, without having received an explanation
of his conduct. He revealed it all to me. It is true. But he did so only with the utmost
cobalistic circumspection. It is necessary to pay his memory the tribute of stating he was a great
zealot.
for the religion of his fathers of the philosophers, and that he would rather have gone through
fire than have profaned his sanctity by taking into his confidence any unworthy prince or
ambitious or immoral man, three types of persons excommunicated for all time by the sages.
Happily I am not a prince.
I have little ambition, and you will presently see that I even have a trifle more chastity
than is requisite for a philosopher."
He found me to be of attractable, inquiring, and fearless disposition.
A dash of melancholy is lacking in me, else I would make all who are inclined to blame
the Comte de Gabales for having released and sealed nothing from me confess that I was
not an unfit civic for the occult sciences.
One cannot make great progress in them and is true without melancholy, but the little I possess
in no wise disheartened him. You have, he told me a hundred times, saturned in an angle,
in his own house, and retrograde some day you cannot fail to be as melancholy as the stage ought
to be, for the wisest of all men as we learn in the Kabbalah had, like you, Jupiter in the
ascendance, nevertheless so powerful as the influence of his Saturn, though far weaker than yours,
that one cannot find proof of his having laughed a single time in all his life.
The amateur is therefore a fine fault with my Saturn and not with the Comte de Gabales.
If I prefer to divulge their secrets rather than to practice them.
If the stars do not do their duty, the Comte is not to blame for it, and I have not sufficient
greatness of soul.
to strive to become master of nature, overthrow the elements, hold communion with supreme
intelligences, command demons, become the father of giants, create new worlds, speak
with God upon his formidable throne, and compel the cherubim, who guard the gate of
terrestrial paradise, who let me stroll now, and then in his alleys, in his eye, and I alone,
whom to blame were to be pitied.
One must not on this account insult the memory of that rare man by saying that he met his
death because he taught me all these things, since the fortunes of war are uncertain, is
may have been overcome in an encounter with some unruly hobgoblin.
Perd Venture, while talking with God upon his flaming throne, he could not keep his
glance from strain to his face.
Now it is written that man may not behold God and live, perhaps he had merely pretended
to die, as is the way of philosophers, who've bane death in one place only to transplant
themselves to another.
So I cannot believe that the manner at which he entrusted his treasures to me permits merit's
punishment.
This is what took place.
As common sense has always made me suspect the existence of much claptrap in the so-called
old cult sciences, I have never been tempted to waste time and pursue perusing books which
treat of them nevertheless.
It does seem quite rational to condemn, without knowing why, all those who are addicted to
these sciences, persons often perfectly sane otherwise, for the most part scholars distinguish
Hence, to avoid being unjust and in order not to fatigue myself with tedious reading,
I determined to pretend to all whom I could learn were interested in the occultism that I was
infatuated with it. From the outset, I had
Greater success than I had even dared hope, since all these gentlemen, however mysterious
and reserved their pride themselves on being, asked nothing better than to parade their theories
and the new discoveries they pretend to have made in nature. It was not long before I became
a confidant of the most important among them, and I had always, some one or the other of them in my
I purposely furnished with the works of most fantastic authors. Without exception,
there was no foreign scholar upon whom I did not have an opinion. In short, in regards to the
science in question, I found myself in a personage of importance. I had its companions, princes,
men of lopty rank, lawyers, beautiful ladies, and ugly ones as well, doctors, prelates, monks,
nuns, in fact people from every walk of life. Some were seeking angels, others the devil,
some of panacea for every ill, some knowledge of the stars, some secrets of divinity, and
almost all the philosophers' stone. They were, to a man, agreed that these mighty
secrets and especially the philosophers' stone are hard to find and few people possess them,
but all entertain a sufficiently good opinion of themselves to fancy that they were the number of the
Happily, the most advanced were at this time, expecting with impatience the arrival of a German,
a nobleman of high rank, and a great cobaltist whose lands lie toward the frontiers of Poland.
He had written to the children of the philosophers of Paris, promising to pay them a visit
when passing through France on his way to England.
I was commissioned to answer this great man's letter. I sent him a map of my horoscope that he
might judge whether I should aspire to the supreme wisdom. Fortunately my map and letter
cause him to do me the honor of replying that I should be one of the first persons whom he would
see in Paris and that heaven willing it would not be his fault if I did not enter the society of
I kept up a regular correspondence with the illustrious German. From time to time,
I propounded to him Waiti, as far as to Mille, while reasoned problems concerning the harmony of
the world, the numbers of Pythagoras, the visions of Saint John, and the first chapter of Genesis.
The profundity of these subjects enraptured him. He wrote me unheard of wonders, and I soon
recognized that I was dealing with a man of very vigorous and vast imagination. I have three or
four score of his letters written in such an extraordinary style that I could never bring
I was alone in the study.
One day I was at marveling at one of the most sublime of these letters.
A very good looking man came bowing gravely to me in a French but with a foreign accent.
Adore, oh my son, adore, very good, and the very good god of the sages and never allow
yourself to become puffed up with pride because he sends one of his children of wisdom to
initiate you into their order and to make you a share in the wonders of its omnipotence.
the novelty of the salutations startled me and for the first time in my life I began to question
whether people may not sometimes cease apparitions nevertheless collecting myself as best as I could
and looking at him as politely as my slight fear permitted I said whoever you may be greeting
is not over this world your visit does me great honor but before I adore the god of the sages
may it please uh you to let me know what sages and what god you refer and if agreeable to you
take this armchair and have the kindness who enlightened me on this God, these sages, this order,
and before, after all this, in the manner of being wisdom, to I have the honor of speaking.
You have referred to me sagely, sir, he replied with a smile, taking the preferred armchair.
You asked me to explain to you the beginning of certain things, which, with your permission, I shall
not touch upon today, the words of the compliment I have paid usages address at the outset to those
who they have determined to open their hearts and reveal their mysteries. From your letters,
I have judged you so advanced that this salutation would not be unknown to you and that you would
Ah, sir, I exclaim recollecting that I had such a great role to play.
How shall I render myself worthy of such kindness? Is it possible that the greatest of all men in
my study, and the renowned Gaba Aliis, honors me with a visit?
I am the least of the sages, he answered gravely, and God, who dispenses the light of wisdom
together with its responsibilities in that measure, with his sovereignty deemed best,
has bestowed upon me a very small portion of the light, in comparison to that of which
I marvel at my fellow initiates.
I expect you to equal them some day, if I dare judge from the map of your horoscope,
with which you honored me.
But why, sir, he added mercifully, are you doing them utmost to get to my good graces
Ah, not for a phantom, I said, but I confess, sir, that I suddenly recall the story of Cardons.
He said his father was one day visited in a study by seven unknown beings clothed in
different colors, who made rather strange statements to him as to the nature and occupation.
I am familiar with the incident which you refer or you interrupt to the comp day.
They were sylphs.
I will tell you about them someday.
They are some kind of ethereal being, and now and then they come to consult the sages
but they do not understand very well.
Cardon is a rattle plate to have published that in his subtitles.
He found the reminiscence among his father's papers.
His father was one of us, realizing that his son was a born babbler.
He did not wish to teach him anything of the moment,
and let him use himself with ordinary astrology,
where if he only knew enough to forecast that his son would be hanged.
So that rascal is a blame for you, having insulted me for being a silt?
Insulted you, I exclaimed, what have I done that should be so unfortunate?
I am not angry with you, he interrupted, you are under no obligation to know all these
elementary spirits are our disciples, that they are only too happy when we condescend
to instruct them, and the lease of our stages is more learned and more powerful than all
of those little fellows.
We will speak of all these matters however at another time.
It is enough today that I have had the satisfaction of seeing you, strive to render yourself worthy
My son the hour-reader generation is at hand it rests solely with you to become a new being
Pray ardently to him who alone has the power to create new hearts that he might give you one capable of great things
To which I teach you that it may inspire me to withhold you none of the mysteries
Then he arose kiss me solemnly and without giving me a chance to reply said adieu my son
I see the members of our order who are in Paris afterward. I shall give you my news meanwhile watch
pray, hope, and be silent. With these words he left my study. On the way out the door,
I expressed my regrets at the shortness of his visit and his cruelty and forsaking me as soon
as he had shown me a spark of his light. But assuring me with great kindness that I would
lose nothing by waiting, he entered his coach and left me a state of amazement with beggars'
I could believe neither my eyes nor my ears.
I am sure I kept saying to myself that this man has an exalted rank, that he's inherited
a yearly income of 50,000 pounds, moreover, he appears to be a person of great accomplishment.
How can it be his lost his head over these occult follies?
He has talked to me about these silphs in an exceedingly cavalier fashion.
Is it not possible that he may be a sorcerer, and I may have not been altogether mistaken
If he is a sorcerer, are they as it about as he seems to be?
I could not solve this riddle, nevertheless I determined to see the matter through to
the end, although I fully realized that I should have to put up with not a few sermons,
but that the demons tormenting him was of a highly moral and pious character.
How is that guys?
Do you like it or no?
I made you wet, did I?
Did I make you wet reading it? I did?
Oh, Destiny. Destiny, come on. I know who that is.
Destiny West. You're that woman that was talking to me in chat like a nut.
Kanye West?
Want to hear a song?
Tryna porn bomb the show like I'm gonna trip
Sayin' wow shit, flexin' hate and fear
But I got glitter nails and a crystal sphere
Doug D talkin' like it's 1952
Racist rents, yeah, I banned you to view
But every troll that clicks my stream
Just feeds the fire in this mystic queen
Trolls make the world go round
But not in my space, not on my crown
They yell, they cry, they talk that smack
But I keep comin' with the tarot pack
Rolls make the world go round, down
Down
Psyche don't fold. You're just another name in the block troll. Scroll.
Trolls make the world go round, but I turn trauma into sound.
You hate my nails, they scratch your fate. I look this good while you sit and hate.
Don't you mess, you feed my flame. Every troll just boosts my name, so go ahead.
Wear that frown. Trolls make the world go round. Down.
storm the chat you try to break me but baby I'm the storm you can't survive and see you next
dream suckers and see you next stream suckers
This
I've been missing in my sleep
Paid I don't know why it's not showing up there. I don't I posted it. I did I have to check I can probably send it to your
inbox, baby
I go hi
Hi
Sorry to me to scare you
This will not do I had to
Put down oh
Guys, let's let's do like we do like a we do like a
Love love song contest. No, it's big. You can be like any girl like your crystal
beta, you know, of course page, you know
Me me and a wig
Christine
Yeah, I did. I'm we're saying prayers out to Jamie's Cowboys. Jamie's Cowboys is in the hospital
I think she had a little car accident. I think she's okay
She had some facial surgery and her T surgery.
So let's all say a prayer for Jamie that she has a quick recovery and she's okay.
Yeah, I want to send some love to Jamie.
Yeah, I think Paige was able to talk to her, I think.
And so she's in contact and she's okay.
But yeah, kind of scary, right?
Who's Rizzy?
Oh, hold on.
Oh, you're yeah, I love you Christine
Yeah, so I don't need to find memberships tonight. And so I think like a bunch of people got let me see who got
Let me see if it's still there. I know it's gone
but uh
You guys even remember who got the membership. I didn't know what
Zimpulse got one. It's been you've been in a little contact with her good. Hope. Yeah. I hope she's doing okay
Love Jamie's butt. You wish her well. Yeah, you've never seen Jamie's butt. You've seen Jamie's butt
I've barely even seen her photo. She's a one avatar. I've never seen her photo otherwise, but I've talked to her a lot on the phone
Well page and Christina here off to play this I'll play this other song again, too because it has page and Christine's
Names in it. Oh, you have to hear this song guys. You have another song
in the wild wild streams where the trolls lurk deep and the chat still beams
there's a light through the chaos a vibe so true that's all because of every single one of you
beat up my sweetheart Persian queen delight with your laugh so loud you light up the night
bomb shell with a beer in hand yeah the streets are rough but we still glide got
my panel verse rider dies right by my side when the drama hits we don't run or
flop now we laugh we read and we climb to
It gets crazy, but we never stop together Panelverse, we're going to the top
Christine, you're the healer The heart's so wide
You check on the broken, you stand with pride Crystal, you're chaos, and I say that with
Sultry you turn up the flame
And Eldo the trucker may be steer this game
From highways to hijinks from terror to tea this ain't just to show its commute
Together, panel
you know it's it's not it's a kind of hard to think you like that you like that it was cute
so if you will just stand out to me like you can see you know
because sometimes on this earth you know it's like sometimes it feels like you don't understand you
Sometimes you meet a few people that might, and you just understand, like, or more than what people think about us, right?
Yeah, I think I mean I have to and then I now is the thing is that I was being I was the thing
I was being so nice before like I was being kind and like Jen I was like it's purposely
Being just like I'll be as nice as I can I was nice and they did that to me imagine. I wasn't mean like imagine how dirty
I mean it gets horrible. I can't be we just get so negative
You see how this is what I'm nice
Imagine if I was actually like in a fighting with people
Right, I know Christine. Yeah, it's like the
I'm kind of thinking about you. Oh
Thank you. I would hug you as a friend too. I hug you all friends
Like we are so much in our mind like we are so much in our mind
It's like ultimately we have this control, right? You used to be nice. Yeah, I mean, I used to be nice, too
It's like everybody still want to be nice, but then it's like, you know, some people
What do they say I get in my like I get my like my feisty energy or something
We're fucking some people just sit there pissing me off. I don't be like I'll start going on
I'm a nice person, but I don't like to be driven in there, but I
Will I will I will always like you know have myself, but you know, I do what
You know, I've never like shied away from like telling the truth about anything, right?
I know, I know, and I've been feeling abused,
and that's why, but I think that's why it's good,
like, because, you know, you're slander when people are,
it's like that can really affect,
that can only affect like just like the people that hate you,
but it's like there's a poison people around you.
And so I understand like a lot of people
will probably like leave the chat and like,
understand that you're pushing him his wheelchair.
Yeah, that's all, I'll take care of each other.
So I understand that,
And I'm lucky just I mean I'm I think I'm just I'm just lucky like that I have just like not only great people around me
But like they're protecting the channel and telling me because there's some people like trying to do things that I wouldn't have caught and like these
People will they'll tell me they're like hey, this is first and showing poor balmy and blah blah. I'll miss it, right?
Yeah, it's about really it really is about the bat like finding a good balance, right?
And it's like, you know, and so sometimes we will go to
virtual extremes in the mind, right?
But no matter where our mind is going,
we can always like, our being on earth is the stability
because our mind will go anywhere.
It's the air, you know, it's like this electricity
and air, it's all over the place.
If we're grounded in the earth,
There's a channel for that to go in the earth and it's like instead of like getting electrocuted. You'll get we'll ground the energy, right?
You sort of ground it through your feet come through your top of your head to your feet, but I hope you like that calm day
Gabales
There's a lot to it. It's like that was it's a very mystery book
You like what you got from it?
So I'll find if I find some other stuff to read to you, too
I was reading something the other night too that had a great point and talked a lot about the power of suggestion
And it's just like if we think how powerful people's suggestions are things people just tell us negative things
And it's like it's programming us to think negative will be like I mean if everybody around us is saying something
Well, our brains will be like well if everyone even if I remember it completely differently
And this must be true like how they're saying right? It's like that our brain will just do that because it's like it's uh
You know it just has to
Not being this like constant like flight or fright flight PTSD mode, right? Only Jamie can lip a lollipop or ice cream. Oh
And then they lick the lollipop
Shorty ladies
We want to go for another sign someone tell me your sign or like your husband's sign or something and I'll read I'll read
I can read about the sex of the astrological sign
If I've ever read I've read some earlier or so might I don't want to
In case I think just everyone in chat since psyche. Oh, thank you. I mean, it's like anybody can send me thing. I appreciate super chats
Just keep a super chats also keep the you know, you should knowing that I'm getting the chats
You know giving up people wanted to donate and and then uh, also, you know
There's ways to uh support the panels now, you know, I'm gonna be offering basically advertisements
Or whatever you'd like to advertise if you'd like for people that would, you know, support in promoting the or
sponsoring the panel for the night, like for example, Summer and Spunky have supported the panels tonight. So I will stay until 2 a.m.
Yeah
Rizzo, I like I like it just put this suggestion out there guys and it's like, you know what?
There are actual fish tacos that I live on the pier. They're the best fish tacos
Um, and I love them you guys. Oh, you want to be okay? So the okay, so we got Leo
Okay, so let's read Leo. I think about it. Did I read something about Leo? It's a so the is a Leo
male a Leo male
Or a Leo female no, let me see you
A Leo male or female beauty
Female let me see but did I read this one already? Let me see
I'm sorry if I did read it. I'm probably
You see yeah, I did I didn't read it, but I'll read just for the other part to you
This one says if you are Leo, it says born rotten
It says I will never have loved another person the way I love myself. It says May West August 17
It says anywhere you go you command attention. That's because you're usually carrying a gun
You vie with Aries for the most obnoxious human award and pick arguments in sports bars to show
everyone who's boss. You are the first to aid friends and family in times of need,
and just as quick to announce to the world how good-hearted you were to offer assistance.
You assume control of every situation where more than one person is gathered.
In an elevator, you position yourself next to the door and push the floor button.
At the grocery store, you instruct the bag boy how to pack the sack.
Your idea of a good career is any profession in which your title is longer than your business card
Leo is a sign of the grade school teacher TV wrestler karaoke champ floating crap game organizer
Lions make the good hair stylist actors and conga lion headers
You don't do solitude instead you head for the nearest party arriving fashionably late
So you can sweep into the room offering your fingertips and air kisses to your loyal fans as you head to the center of the action your
Your nature is so theatrical that you can't bear the thought of being just one of the crowd and you will stand on your head or someone else's back to grab the spotlight.
Your home is your castle where you rule by intimidation. You spend your evenings scolding your family, yelling at the dog, hanging up on your mother, your temper is like a solar flare.
It flashes out, singling the ears of the hopeless persons who dare to disagree, then dissipates
just as quickly.
Because you have a selective memory, you think you're calm, cool, collected, and will beat
the hell out of anyone who disagrees.
In romance, you have the finesse of a sailor returning from a 12-month cruise.
You'll go home with anyone who offers to buy you a $6 beer and tells you you have great
hair.
The next day, you bore your friends with tales of sexual conquests that everyone knows
or lies.
What you don't know is that secretly everyone hopes you get eaten by a crocodile.
Your checking account serves as a clearinghouse between your paycheck and creditors, and you file for bankruptcy
so often you're banned from using credit cards until 2052.
Your favorite game is Follow the Leader, which you're the head of the group, but instead of Captain Courageous,
you are more like the captain of the Titanic. You know where you're going and invariably leads everyone to disaster.
In real life, John Wayne was a Gemini, however every role he ever played was pure Leo, always
strong, sometimes air again, his character always knew just what they wanted and how
to get it.
So do you.
You are lively, sincere, and elegant.
Your independent nature is most contented when you are fighting for a cause or an underdog.
However, since your biases can be as large as your virtues, you need to learn how to
redirect some of your powerful energy.
Give your attention to others versus calling it to yourself.
Focus on taking time to understand more and more, and criticize less, and not a sign.
Oops, shit.
In the meantime, anyone who wants to wrestle with a lion will soon find that you are still king of the jungle.
You have you walk all over the earth signs with no fear one swipe of your powerful claws stops tourists and it's charging tracks
Virgo and singly be knows how to defer to your royal bearing you verbally shake capricorn by the hairy neck until it's limp with fear
You definitely have a feline taste for seafood and one glimpse of a gleaming fang sends you petulant Pisces diving for cover
Should a crackled crab scuttle out to bite your paw you snap out in the tiny in the saddened afternoon snack and
The air signs Gemini, Aquarius, and Libra simply can't ruffle your fur, no matter how they
hardly posture and blow.
You and fellow fire signs, airs and Sagittarius, understand each other at a soul level.
Yours is the philosophy, work hard, play hard.
You believe in life.
Up to the fullest, you see no reason to let anyone tell you differently.
You're totally independent, have the serendipitous fortune of being in the right place at the
right time.
Let the rest of the world clip coupons and save for a rainy day.
Years from now, when your old lovers and ex-friends are living off their pensions and eating two-for-one
canned chili, you can generously use some of that million-dollar jackpot you hit in Vegas
to send along a case of beluga caviar and a magnum of Don Perignon.
I was trying to read for the person that asked, that was kind of interesting.
What do you still mean guys?
What do I just mean? What do you meanies?
I don't know if I like it.
So let me see what I can do first with food. Time for the incantation,
God, hold on God draw the ritual circle. I'm going to show you something God,
I'm going to show you something, hold on. How about this God, do you like this chick?
I bet you will.
Get away from the circle, get away from the circle, guys.
He's doing an incantation.
On this day of darkness, in the land of despair,
let all those who try to take this channel down,
turn their frown upside down.
Like that?
Yes, yes, yes.
Okay.
I think that calls for a little sagey, like, you know,
Then the prayer so that takes this takes the first week smoke some weed and that takes them to the prayer with the smoke
And then we're gonna do some sage and that who is that? Oh, that is her name is Samantha Ronson. She is
You'll God you got to see this movie
She's beautiful
You hit that. Yeah, she's gorgeous. You'll you would love that movie. She has it's really cool movie
She has a really gorgeous costume of that. It's made one woman made the whole movie in
California, but it looks like it's from the 70s, but it's actually like recent really I think the 2017 or 18
Is it a hammer film a hammer like I wouldn't mean hammer like I
Don't know it's like a think she like this
It's hot. It's hot. She's I think she's Australian. She might be English or Australian. You're right here. Yeah, she is English or Australian
She's gorgeous though. This movie's a trip though. It's
What year was it it was it was shot in 35 millimeter film though and it was shot it was 2016
So it's like yeah nine years old. Yeah, it's really good. It's the sex for ya
She's uh, you know, the men just seem to die around her. She doesn't know it. She doesn't know what happens
She's kind of, she's very, she's very confused about the whole thing.
She's just running, you know, starting new lives and stuff.
Very interesting.
Hey, you're welcome, Boston Strong.
Hey, come back and say hi and stuff like that.
You know, I haven't seen you for a while,
but congratulations on getting the gifted membership,
gifted that five memberships tonight.
Boston Strong got one and a few other people.
So congratulations to everyone that did.
Which is getting freaky between the sheets that sounds like some kind of some kind of white supremacist movie. I don't see that one
The sheets free in freaky or freaky or freaky like a freaky person
Today it is freaky fright. Oh, no, it's actually but I think it's like a
I don't know what is today the clan which I don't know
But I literally have a book about the Black Clansman.
It's about this black guy that was in the Klan.
And so we obviously have some weird going on there.
Let's see, Timu, a discount, 99% off.
That sounds like a good discount.
Let me see.
What can I get?
I need a vacuum.
This is not true
He moves stuff look at the female black man. Yeah, there's a black hands man
It's like he I guess he infiltrated the clan. It was a movie. How the black lands are
bodies of the cemetery. Hey, look what I found. Guys, look at this. Can someone take a picture of
this? Look. Look what I found. You read it? You read it?
It's classy sassy and a little bad assy.
First classy sassy, right?
Very cute.
Very good to be like doing boss that house. How does your wife boss? Come on. Let's hear you. It's waiting forever
Boss left boss is sort of say hi for the membership. I think I think you probably just failed that's what happens
Here's a say hi
Now then yeah, I think you left
This is a nice golf shirt, Jaggedy's shirt.
Read his wife. So you're talking about Boston? I don't know. He's from Boston. He probably has like a
beehive hairdo or something, right?
Guys, does it all make sense now? It all makes sense now, right?
I like this one.
This is pretty cool, oh, you know her?
I'm sure.
I like when they're like $5, not like $12.
Let's see.
Have you ever seen the picture of the cherubim?
I mean, do you want to see what the angels really look like?
This is supposed to be the angels that will scare you guys.
Do you want to see what the angels really look like?
I'm sure you want to meet the angel.
Guys, have you ever heard the same women must serve men?
Which they must they must I mean they want to I don't know
It's yeah
My first pet
This can go low on my speedo guys
So you get that to go low on the speedo can get that
black outfit
This reminds me of Emma right here. She was more of like, you know, she's not that good.
Ja, diese Künze.
Das immer, ja.
What's up? Oh my god, I can't stop. I guess
Don't read the catool aid or drink it
Relia princess Raleigha princess Raleigha
God, you got appetite.
Because the cookies are not as good.
This one didn't have any screw cookies.
Yeah.
Yeah, Big Debra.
I think I dated Big Debra, but she was
Linda at the time, but she was the same person.
Well, I think that's enough.
You love veggie and big woman?
Do what?
I dated a 250 pound woman.
She was a Leo.
She was very, very feisty and overwhelming.
I did make her squirt like the Niagara Falls ones.
Considered that my initiation into the world.
That's like my second birth.
I don't need to have a third one.
Related to that one.
Okay, well, I mean, I was just looking at the t-shirts.
They have some games and stuff.
They have tarot cards and stuff.
They have really expensive tarot cards
and they have really cheap tarot cards.
And so they're kind of like worried about the cheap ones.
Just so they're not like the knockoffs and stuff, I'm not sure.
But they do have some regular price stuff, but.
They sell all kinds of magic stuff in these places now. It's like it's so weird. It's like all this mainstream, right?
God I love you God. Thank you for coming. Okay. I'll talk to you soon. You're my buddy, okay?
Steampunk glasses
Okay. Well, is anybody here? I think Gotti's the one person was the one person talking. Why are you guys so quiet?
I'm gonna read you some more stories. I mean, you want some reading or talk? Come on. Where's everybody at the panel open to you?
Love you Gotti. Thank you for coming. Okay. How about this one? Gotti, how about this one?
You come to you just don't tell anybody you come here. You come here. It's okay. You don't have to tell anybody you can hide I
Appreciate you Nick
Sorry, sorry, I haven't I've been able to score you a free membership, but
Okay, we have one more hour guys I
Will keep my words up and I'll leave the panel. Oh my gosh the panel is open. I think I thought I pinned it
I'm so sorry. Well, if I didn't pin it
I don't want to say anything.
OK, I need it back.
I need it back.
I think I need to get this looking back in.
I can get one.
I think I can get one now.
I should have just taken 50 bucks.
Back this up, right?
Game, game.
So you're gonna hit a bunch of cocksuckers?
Why are you being like that, Boston?
You're mad at me?
Boston, I didn't do anything to you.
I mean, I was like, I was like, always kind, right?
Are you terminating deermen or something?
Anybody ever shopped at the tiktok shop?
Okay
So guys, you know, Kate's going to be doing a show with Tony Allied Master Computer on Sunday.
So it appears that I heard that today on her on Kate's show.
So, wow, it appears that they are some bosom buddies now, right?
how are we doing guys let's see okay well everyone's being quiet i don't know why everyone's
being quiet so i'll just like tell us a little night time stories and we can go to him
everyone to come up i'll like i'll extend um her time into the next show okay
you're okay okay
Everyone's just quiet. It seems like I just want to like they're just like looking at me. There's chillin, okay
You know, I get a little paranoid sometimes
Okay, so let's see
Binding this little story
you're listening okay I'm sorry if I'm like a little bit slow I'm just like looking at for
like a cool booktree so this one's I think I'm gonna say I like short things
I don't like like a really long long stuff but I have a lot of interesting stuff I'll find something
There's a book called Understanding Colts.
It's an ASMR.
I'll read this book called Understanding Colts.
Do you wanna hear this one?
I'll read this to you so you can.
And if you guys, if you like this,
you know, maybe just like a,
let me know by donating a super chat
or something like that.
So I'll do more of it,
but I'll read this like a,
called Understanding Colts.
The Guide to Analysis to Protection,
Risk and Recovery from Destructive Colts.
Amanda Bunn-Arx.
has ever since ever had an experience with a cult or controlling relationship,
have a friend or relative caught up in a black and white, all-or-nothing conspiracy cult,
multi-level marketing, religious, or political group.
Hi, Destiny.
To help them or yourself,
You need to learn how the mind works so that people can be programmed into a destructive authoritarian cult.
Not all are destructive. Some are harmless. There are explicit strategies, patterns, and behaviors used by cultic groups to recruit new members and manipulate and control them.
The most vital step in guarding you and your loved ones is learning more about what a cult is, how they work, and lasting serious after-effects of being involved with one.
Nobody joins a cult voluntarily. They are recruited into it. There's an absence of informed consent. Everyone has vulnerabilities
Possible situational vulnerabilities including illness the passing of a friend or family member break up of an important relationship loss of a job
Or moving to another city state or country
Individual vulnerabilities may include high him to hypnotize ability strong ability for concentration and vivid imagination learning disorders
or autism spectrum disorders. Exorbitant use of hypnosis meditation or other activities can induce
an altered state of consciousness. These in turn increase vulnerability to being recruited by a
cult, except if there are solid decisive reasoning, media literacy, and a good supportive network,
often which can help a person stay grounded, right? Other risks consist of learning and
communication disorders, drug and alcohol problems, trauma, unresolved sexual issues,
There are even 21 first-century contributors, the C-19, severe economic disruption, isolation,
lack of touch, social political polarization, increased time online, internet addiction,
recruitment into extreme conspiracy theories and cult scams.
If in a vulnerable state you fall into one of the numerous recruitment strategies, some
Through a friend or from a community or then again, you might end up recruited online from social posts
YouTube's websites videos discussion forums dating apps movies or video games
You like this? Okay
So it says
Part one, examining cults. It says, what exactly is a cult? Destructive people and cults use deception and undue influence to make individuals reliant in obedience, a group ought not to be viewed as a cult only in light of its unorthodox beliefs.
It is typical authoritarian, headed by a person or group of people within your complete control of followers. Cult influence is intended to upset an individual's authentic identity and replace it with a new identity.
There are many sorts of cults, political, religious, self-help, large group awareness trainings,
mini-cults, family or one-on-one, multi-level marketing, MLM, conspiracy theory, commercial
and labor sex trafficking.
Influence and control. Influence is everywhere. Parenting, relationships, media, education, politics, business, religion, psychotherapy.
Be that as it may, influence can be enormously positive and helpful as well as a detriment.
It is important to recognize the difference between due and undue influence.
Due influence involves informed consent, your choice, right to question, listening with your inner voice, freedom to interact with anyone, free will, freedom to leave.
You are not allowed to question and your inner voice is suppressed.
It includes isolation and control, fear and coercion, and enslavement.
Undue influence can present as a subtile, for instance,
you are given the illusion of informed choice and control.
To an ever-increasing extent, I've seen clients who have been abused by the use of hypnosis
and NLP, neuro-liquistic programming, particularly by unfit life coaches.
Indu influence can, then again, be extreme or overt, like kidnapping or torment.
In any case, it's all undue influences destructive.
It is otherwise called mind control or thought reform.
Okay, so it says cult psychology, cult leaders and individuals who will be obedient to them
and their principles.
They search for approaches to break people.
They want individuals who will work hard and then long hours for little or no pay.
They are willing slaves.
Authoritarian religious cults frequently use individuals for labor trafficking.
When the psyche is controlled, a victim might be happy and seems to offer the profit.
The seeds you suffer for profit for the benefit for the group right for members joy comes from great performance from the group
Alongside elitist thinking because leaving they have the truth the most ideal way of life yet strict compliance is required
They're controlled by fear and guilt and might be stuck with no chance to get out
Identity change under a new influence doesn't erase the individual's old identity, but instead creates a new identity to suppress the old one.
After various kinds of manipulation, the creation of a new identity is done bit by bit by former and formal indoctrination sessions, casually by members, videos, games, movies, publications, social and digital media.
Behavior modification techniques are employed such as reward punishment, thought stopping and control of environment, isolation, restriction of access to others.
And then the new identity is reinforced and the old identity
suppress.
It causes this a lot of problems, right?
So I'm just looking for the psychology of cults.
There's a lot of reasons.
Women are more likely to join a cult.
Newcomers are love-bombed, right?
It's like narcissism, it's like a narcissistic relationship, but it's an organization, which is
even scarier. Okay, that was that book. So interesting.
Might leave in a few, I'm gonna see if there's any food I can get. I'm kind of getting a little bit hungry.
Or at least a copy maybe.
I'm going to read, okay, I'm going to read you the, I'm going to read you the menu to DoorDash.
I'm trying to find some food real quick. I'll, I'll, I'll read, I'll read you.
So there was this guy looking for food from DoorDash, so he looked at the app.
Now the app, there were some food offers, okay, so there was a deal.
Who would it be?
Copy for sure food. Yes. So we see Taco Bell. It's Taco Bell to have coffee. So let me see this place doesn't have coffee don't know
No, no, Carl's Jr. Or McDonald. Okay, so we'll be Carl's Jr. Cuz I
Don't want the queso french burger
Actually, I just want coffee. I think I've done a couple coffees
I'm gonna have good coffee. They have like just like arabica
I want like a delicious like
Coffee milkshake. Oh, here we go
Oh
Shit hold on
Guys, did you see anything guys? Did you see anything? Yeah, I think it was a poor mama. Was it you see anything?
Okay, I can get like a I get like a vanilla milkshake I can pour the coffee in it. Let's see. I'll be good and get a
Vanilla milkshake you saw nothing. Yeah, I got it before he was able to but it was it's an Apollo creed
But it said then it said another name for like the person and it's a good name
I know but it wasn't that I don't think of the person. Yeah, I didn't see anything
Okay, so that how about I get a?
Copy right the Arapa coffee be large
five bucks, okay
The coffee and then what else?
You can get like a jalapeno poppers or you get
Chicken stars
Triple Diablo cheeseburger. Yeah, I didn't see this I didn't see shit
This foolish porn bombers
I'll just, I'll just say, I don't have to eat right now.
I'll eat, I'll get like a little bit later
because it's better to deal if I wait a few hours.
And I still have, oh, I finished beer.
I have a little drinks and stuff, okay.
Okay, so who's here?
Why isn't he gonna be talking?
Hey, what's up Evil Ron McDonald?
I like Evil Ron McDonald.
So I'm nothing, okay.
So I'll read, I'll read, I'll read, I'll read.
Let's continue reading.
Secret Empire is this one.
It didn't shoot behind the power of what?
Oh, this looks good.
Actually, it's about the 9th Templar, so I can't really read about it, so it's controversial
or secret.
Okay.
The Book of Forbidden Knowledge.
It was forbidden, so let's share it.
Oh, okay.
Okay, book of forbidden knowledge. Let's go to the beginning. It says,
divination or how to obtain knowledge of future events. Any person fasting on mid-summer eve
and sitting on the church porch will at midnight see the spirits of the persons of that parish,
who will die that year come and knock on the church door in order to succession of which they will
One of these watchers, there being several in company, fell into a profound sleep so
that he could not be waked, whilst in this state his ghost was seen by the rest of the
companions knocking at the church door.
Any unmarried woman, fasting on Midsummer's Eve, and on midnight laying on a clean cloth
with bread, cheese, and ale, and sitting down as if going to eat, the street door being
left open, the person whom she is afterward to marry will come into the room and drink
to her by bowing, and afterward, filling the glass, will leave it on the table, and making
another bow retire.
On St. Agnes' night, the 21st of January, take a row of pins and pull out every one,
one after another, saying a pot or nostre, or sticking a pin in your sleeve, and you will
dream of him, and you shall marry.
Another method of seeing a future spouse in a dream, the party inquiry must lie in a different
country, from which he commonly resides, and a going to bed must knit the left garter about
the right leg it's talking.
and letting the other garter in stocking alone as you rehearse the following verse, and at every comma, knit it or not.
This knot I knit, to know a thing I know not yet, that I may see, the man that shall my husband be, how he goes and what he wears, and what he does all days and years.
Accordingly in a dream, he will appear with the insignia of his trade or profession, another
performed by a charming the moon, the dust, at the first appearance of the new moon, immediately
after the nearest day, go out in the evening, and stand in the spears of the gator still,
and looking out in the moon, repeat the following lines,
All hail to thee, all hail to thee, I pre thee, good moon, reveal to me, this night,
The party will then dream of their future husband, a slice of the bridal cake thrice
thrown through a wedding ring, will land under the head of the unmarried woman, and will
make the same dream of a future husband, the same as practice in the north with a piece
of the groaning cheese.
How to Receive Oracles by Dreams
He who would receive true dreams shall keep a pure undisturbed and imaginative spirit,
and so compose it that he may be made worthy of knowledge and government of the mind.
For such a spirit is most fit for prophesizing, and is most clear glass of all things.
When, therefore, we are in a sound body, not disturbed in mind, our intellect not made dull
by heavy meals and strong drink, not sad through poverty, not provoked through lust, not incited
by any advice, not stirred up by wrath or anger, nor being irreligious or profanely inclined,
nor given to levity nor loss and drunkenness, but chastely going to bed, fall asleep, and
then our pure divine soul, being free from all the evils above recited, and separated
from the hurtful thoughts, and now freed by dreaming, is endowed with the divine spirit
as an instrument, and does receive these beams and representations which are darted upon,
darted down as if it were to shine forth from the divine mind into itself a deifying glass.
There were four kinds of true dreams.
matunin, i.e. slapping, sleeping, and walk waking. The second, that which one sees concerning another.
The third, that whose interpretation is shown, and the same dreamer in the nocturnal vision.
And lastly, that which is related to the same dreamer in the nocturnal vision. But natural
things and their own co-mixtures do likewise belong to wise men. And we often use such to
by dream, which they are neither by perfumed unctions,
meets drinks, rings, seals, et cetera.
Now, those who are desirous to receive oracles through a dream
let them make themselves a ring of the sun or Saturn
for those purpose.
One second, okay, I'll move that.
There are likewise images of dreams
which being put under the head.
of going to sleep to effectively give true dreams of whatever the mind has before determined or consulted upon, the practice of which follows.
You should make an image of the sun, the figure where a misbehave man sleeping under the bosom of an angel,
and you will make, when Leo ascends, and the sun being the ninth house in Aries,
you must write upon the figure the name of the effect desired, and the hand of the angel the name of the character and intelligence of the sun.
which is Michael. Let the image be made in Virgo ascending, Mercury being fortunate in Aries in the
Ninth or Gemini ascending, Mercury being fortunate in the Ninth House Aquarius, let him be received
by Saturn with a fortunate aspect, and let the name of the spear which is Raphael be written upon
it. Let the same likewise be made, Libra ascending Venus being received from Mercury and Gemini in
the Ninth House and right upon it the name of the Angel of Venus which is Anayel.
Again, you may make the same image, Aquarius ascending. Saturn, fortunately, possessing
the strength of this situation, exaltation, which is Zebra, and there is written upon
the name of the angel of Saturn, which is Caustiel. The same may be made with cancer
ascending, the moon being received by Jupiter and Venus and Pisces, and being fortunately
placed in the ninth house.
So that interesting guys so guys I think we've climbed like had a quiet night and maybe there's other people on so I'm gonna
Just end right now. I give summer an extra 30 minutes of piano panel time for the next show. I love you guys